4K资源来源:Hao4k影音
-专注4K家庭影音 服务千万发烧友-
更多4K蓝光原盘:www.Hao4k.vip
‎（波士顿警局）
‎斯宾塞先生 你准备好‎用自己的语言向本庭讲述
[judge] Mr. Spenser, are you preparedto tell the court, in your own words,
‎3月20日下午发生的事了吗？
what happened on the afternoonof March 20th?
‎是的 法官大人
[Spenser] Yes, Your Honor.
‎请讲
[judge] Please proceed.
‎我让我的搭档开车送我‎去约翰博伊兰警监家
[Spenser] I had my partner drive meto the home of Captain John Boylan.
‎你的上司？
[judge] Your commanding officer?
‎是的
[Spenser] That's right.
‎我有理由相信 博伊兰警监
I had prior reason to believe
that Captain Boylanwas intentionally burying
‎刻意阻挠对格洛莉娅维希涅夫斯基‎谋杀案的调查…
the murder investigationof Gloria Weisnewski--
‎斯宾塞先生 请着重讲述
[judge] Mr. Spenser,please focus on the events that transpired
‎3月20日下午发生的事
-on the afternoon of March 20th.-[knocking on door]
‎想要质问他那项调查的事
and attempted to question himabout the investigation.
‎你来干什么？
The hell are you doing here?
‎在随后发生的争执中…
[Spenser] And the ensuing argument...
‎你可以在门外等着
[Boylan] Can't wait outsidethe front door?
‎-所有人都知道是怎么回事‎-不关你的…
[Spenser sighs] I mean,everybody knows what happened.
‎从我家滚出去！
Get out of our house!
‎嘿 滚出去！
Hey! Get out of here.Get the fuck out of our house--
[grunts]
‎我始终很清楚 这样做违反了法律
[Spenser] At all times, I knew that theseactions were in violation of the law
‎违反了我发誓会遵守的‎波士顿警察行为准则
and the code of conduct that I sworeto obey as a Boston police officer.
‎那么照我的理解‎对于扰乱治安的指控
[judge] So, it is my understandingthat you are pleading guilty
‎你表示认罪
to the charge of disturbing the peace?
‎是的 法官大人
[Spenser] Yes, Your Honor.
‎对于一级骚扰的指控 你是否认罪？
[judge] How do you plead on the countof harassment in the first degree?
‎-放开他！‎-我认罪
-[woman] Get off him!-[Spenser] Guilty.
‎对于严重袭警的指控 你是否认罪？
[judge] And how do you plead on the countof aggravated assault of a police officer?
‎我认罪
[Spenser] Guilty.
‎在我对你作出判决之前‎你还有什么想要补充的吗？
[judge] Before I sentence you,
is there anything furtherthat you would like to add?
‎有
[Spenser] Yes.The son of a bitch deserved it.
‎那个混蛋是罪有应得
‎（五年后）
[gate buzzing]
‎（监狱）
[indistinct announcement on PA]
‎（《中型/重型货车系统基础》）
‎（巨柱仙人掌）
‎怎么样 斯宾塞？
What do you say, Spense?
‎嗨 呆子
-Hey, Squeeb.-[grunts]
‎跟你说个有趣的小知识
Hey, new little fun fact for you.
‎知道吗？‎巨柱仙人掌的寿命超过150年
You know, Saguaro cactuslives for over 150 years?
‎在亚利桑那州 你要是砍掉一颗‎可能要坐一年的牢 想想看
Now, you cut one down in Arizona,
you can do a year in prison. Imagine that?
‎妈的
Shit. [chuckles]
‎我知道这里有些抢劫犯
I know guys that rob people in here
‎-刑期都没那么长‎-对吧？
-doin' less time than that.-[chuckling] Right?
‎快要出去了 感觉如何？
How does it feel gettin' out?
‎有几晚睡不着觉 不过除此之外…
I haven't slept in a few nights.But other than that...
‎你怎么样 呆子？感觉如何？
How you doin', Squeeb? How you feelin'?
‎感觉像个无期徒刑犯
I feel like a lifer.
‎你知道 很多人都有这种感觉
You know, a lot of guys feel that way.
‎但是你不一样
But you're different.
‎有几个警察会和普通囚犯关在一起？
How many cops get to dotheir time in gen pop?
‎没有
Zero.
‎我一个也想不出来
I can't think of one.
‎我是说…
But, I mean, that's probably whyyou're so popular in here.
‎也许这就是‎你在这里如此受欢迎的原因
‎我受欢迎？
I'm popular? Wow, I had no idea.
‎你不说我还不知道
‎出去以后打算干点什么？
[Squeeb] What're you gonna dowhen you get out?
‎-回到真实的世界以后？‎-嗯
[Spenser] Back in the real world?
‎去芬威球场
Yeah. Go to Fenway Park,
‎吃一大块多汁的肋眼牛排？
you know, get a big-ass, juicy rib eye.
‎你有女朋友 对吧？
You got a girl, right?
‎有 她叫珀尔
I got a girl. Her name is Pearl.
‎也许我会躺在床上‎让她舔遍我的全身
Yeah, I'm probably just gonnalay down in my bed
and let her lick me all over.
‎珀尔？
Pearl. Sounds like an old lady's name, no?
‎听着像是老太太的名字
‎她确实不年轻了
You know, she's a little older.She makes up for it in loyalty.
‎好在她够忠诚
‎最近怎么样 书呆子？
'Sup, bookworm?
‎不怎么样
Not much.
‎雅利安国是如何对待大家的？
How's Aryan Nation treatin' everybody?
‎国情咨文仍然给力吗？
State of the Union still strong? [scoffs]
‎你知道 我们只是想让你明白
You know, we just wannalet you know how important it is
‎你必须离开波士顿 永远别回来
that you're gettin' out of Bostonand never comin' back,
‎去开卡车 或者随便干什么
drivin' a truckor doin' whatever the hell you're doin'.
‎对 有人托我们给你送一条临别赠言
Yeah, we have a little, uh,goin' away message for you.
‎给我的？
For me?
‎好吧 肯定不是犯人托你们的
Well, can't be from the guys in here.
‎他们喜欢我 对吧？
They like me, right?
‎说吧 是谁托你们带话？
So, who's sending the message?
‎收拾他们 斯宾塞
Fuck 'em up, Spenser.
["Foreplay/Long Time" playing]
[men groaning]
♪ It's been such a long time ♪
‎好了 来吧
All right, come on.
[both grunt]
‎你踢我 老兄？
Did you just kick me, bro?
‎操！
[grunts] Fuck!
‎滚出波士顿！
[man] Get the fuck outta Boston!
‎为什么要踢我 老兄？
Why you gotta kick me, bro?
[both grunting]
‎是谁托你们带话？
[Spenser] Who sent the message?
♪ I've got to keep onChasin' a dream, yeah ♪
♪ I've gotta be on my way ♪
‎（四级防范禁闭：公共区域）
[guard] Come on, man.
‎行了
All right, all right, hold on!
‎斯宾塞
Spense. [chuckles]
[Spenser grunts]
‎算你走运 这次是自卫 斯宾塞
You're lucky it was self-defense, Spenser.
♪ Well, I'm takin' my timeI'm just movin' on ♪
‎把手放进去扫描
[guard] Put your hand through.
‎你身上只有指纹是独一无二的 懒鬼
Your fingerprints arethe only unique thing about you, shitbag.
‎不是吧？五年前我入狱时‎你就是这样说的 想点新段子吧
Seriously? You said that five years agowhen I got here.
Why don't you get some new material?
‎-不出一个月我们还会见面‎-祝你愉快
-I'll see you in about a month or less.-Have a nice day.
‎嘿 你去上卡车驾驶课的时候‎帮个忙行吗？
Hey, you wanna do me a favorwhen you start that truck driving class?
‎给我的贝蒂姑妈带句话：‎“让你妹妹去死吧”
Tell my Aunt Betty I said,"Go fuck your sister."
‎你家人真够奇葩的 莱尼
You got a very weird family,don't you, Lenny?
♪ Well, I'm takin' my timeI'm just movin' along ♪
[breathes deeply]
‎嘿
[chuckling] Hey! You made it.
‎你熬出头了
‎外面很不错吧？
-Nice out here, huh?-[sighs]
‎花点时间好好享受这种感觉
Take a minute, enjoy it.
‎争取别再进去了
Try and stay on this side for a while.
‎哇 这辆里维埃拉一点都不显旧
Wow. Riviera hasn't aged a day.You gonna let me drive?
‎能让我来开吗？
‎你还会开吗？
You remember how?
[engine revs]
‎见鬼 上车！
Oh, shit! Get in the car! Hurry up!
‎-快点 我不想让她看见我‎-怎么了？
-Why? What's up? Why?-Come on, I don't want her to see me.
‎快点 走了！
Hurry up! Come on, let's go!
‎你干什么？人家大老远的开车来看你
What are you doing?She drove all this way to see you.
‎五年监禁？
[woman] Five years in prison?
‎嘿！
-[Spenser] Hey!-[thuds]
‎你就不能少管闲事吗？
Why can't you just stay out ofother people's businesses, huh?
‎这下你高兴了吧？
How do you like that?
‎我爱你！
I love you!
‎我他妈的爱死你了！
I love you so fuckin' much!
‎见鬼
Shit.
‎这里不能停车 女士
[guard] Can't park there, ma'am.
‎趴下！
[whispers] Get down!
‎我还没准备好见她
‎她大老远的来看你
[man] You know, she cameall this way to see you.
‎亨利 我只是没有准备好
[Spenser] Henry, I'm just not ready.
‎他妈的铁石心肠
Heart made of granite 'causeI find out from someone at the car wash
‎我还是听洗车场的人说他今天出狱
that he got out of prison today?
‎好吧 肖申克 我把车挪走 妈的
All right, Shawshank.I'll move my fuckin' car.
Fuck!
[sighs]
‎我这就走
I'm gonna kill him.
[tires screeching]
["Supernatural Thing" playing]
♪ Your love, your love ♪
♪ Supernatural thing ♪
♪ When we touch ♪
♪ Give me such a funny feelingIn my brain ♪
♪ Oh, babe ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ Your love, your love ♪
♪ Supernatural thing ♪
‎当年我老爸用八千美元买下这个地方
[Henry] Back in the day, my old manbought this place for 8,000 bucks.
‎现在一层就值150万美元
Now it's worth $1,500,000 per floor.
‎卖了吧 实现梦想
Sell it, live the dream.Come to Arizona with me.
‎跟我去亚利桑那
‎不
[Henry chuckles] Nah.My dream is to die in my bed, right here.
‎-我的梦想是死在这里的床上‎-斯宾塞！
-[car lock chirps]-[man] Spenser!
‎还好吧 德里斯科？
What's up, Driscoll?
‎斯宾塞 过来
-[laughing] Spenser. Come here.-What's up?
[laughs]
‎抱歉我不能常去沃尔波尔看你 兄弟
I'm sorry I couldn't visit youmore at Walpole, brother.
‎听着 你能来我很高兴‎谢谢你送那些书给我
Look, I'm glad you came up.
‎甜甜圈？
-Donuts?-I wanna keep you on your toes.
‎-我想让你保持机警‎-嘿！
-Hey.-[Driscoll chuckling]
‎好样的 在牢里熬过来了
Impressive how you did your time.
‎作为曾经的警察‎我在牢里很受欢迎
As a former police officer,
I was very, very popular in there.That's for sure.
‎接下来有何打算？这是个大问题
Man. So, what's next?That's the big question.
‎听着 我要离开这里
Look, I'm gettin outta here, you know?
‎这里没有我想要的东西‎我打算去开半挂车
There ain't shit for me here.I'm gonna drive a semi, you know?
‎看看日落什么的
Look at sunsets. Shit like that.
‎哦 也许这样最好
Ah, maybe it's for the best.
‎这里仍有很多警察想要收拾你
There's still a lot of cops around herewho'd love to put a mark on you.
‎听着 如果有人骚扰我‎我知道给谁打电话
Well, I get in a hassle,I know who to call.
‎没错
That's fuckin' right.
‎好吧
All right, man, welcome home, brother.
‎欢迎回家 兄弟 我爱你
‎很高兴见到你 兄弟
I love you. Nice to see you, brother.
‎今天过得怎么样 西莫利先生？
How you doin' today, Mr. Cimoli?
‎过得不错
I'm good.
‎-替我问候艾琳和你的儿子‎-没问题 斯宾塞
-Say hi to Irene and the boys.-You got it.
‎去看看你的女朋友吧
Let's go see your girlfriend.
‎珀尔
[Spenser] Pearl.
‎珀尔 宝贝
Pearly, baby. Hey.
‎嘿
‎珀尔
Pearly.
‎亨利 她看都不看我 她不理我
Henry, she won't even look at me.
She gave me the cold shoulder.
‎宝贝 抱歉我离开了你‎我知道五年的时间太长了
Baby, I'm sorry that I was gone.I know five years is way too long.
‎对她来说是35年
Thirty-five years from her perspective.
‎你再也不需要过寒冬了
No more cold winters for you.
‎你可以把小爪子埋在沙漠里
You're gonna keep yourlittle paws in the desert,
‎你会在沙地里追逐小兔子 好吗？
you're gonna chase littlebunny rabbits in the sand. Huh?
‎亚利桑那州没有小兔子
There's no bunny rabbits in Arizona.
‎只有蛇和蝎子 她活不过一个礼拜
They got snakes and scorpions.She wouldn't last a week.
‎亨利 你闭嘴行吗？
You gotta shut the fuck up, okay?
‎我只想清静一会儿
I'm just tryin' to have a moment here
‎向我的小姑娘道歉‎因为我没有陪在她身边
and apologizefor my absence to my baby girl.
‎我们去亚利桑那州 好吗？
We're gonna go to Arizona, all right?
‎我去开卡车 再也不离开你了
I'm gonna drive a truckand I'm never gonna let you go.
‎我会一只手扶着方向盘‎一只手抚摸你
I'll have one hand on the wheeland the other hand on you.
‎我会在座椅旁边放一个小床‎这就对了
We'll put a little bedright beside my chair.
‎这就对了
-Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.-[Pearl whining]
‎宝贝 你有口臭‎我不是叫你买洁牙棒吗？
Baby, you got the breath.
Didn't I tell you to buy the Greenies?
‎你没买防止口臭的狗狗饼干吗？
You didn't get herthe dog biscuits for her breath?
‎我要进屋了
[Henry] Uh, I'm going inside.
‎嘿
[Spenser] Hey, thank youfor my very own room.
‎谢谢你给我单独的房间
[breathes deeply]
[hip-hop music playing over speakers]
‎（欢迎回来！）
[hip-hop music continues playing]
‎喂！
Yo!
‎亨利！
Henry!
‎-干嘛？‎-你说过给我单独一间房
-What?-You said I had my own room.
‎霍克 这是斯宾塞
Hawk, this is Spenser.Spenser, this is Hawk.
‎斯宾塞 这是霍克
‎以后你们就是室友了
You two are gonna be roommates.
‎用完马桶要随手冲 食物要贴上标签
Toilets are flushed at all times.
‎我没说喝酒 谁都不许喝酒
and if there's going to beany drinking, I instigate it.
‎现在 你们两个彼此熟悉一下
Now, I'd like you twoto get to know each other.
[hip-hop music playing over headphones]
[cell phone vibrating and chiming]
[Hawk clicking tongue]
‎我的乖女儿来了
[kisses] There's my girl.
‎好的
Yes.
‎你爱爹地 对吧？
You love Daddy. You love Daddy, don't you?
[Hawk chuckles]
‎谁是大怪兽？
Who's a big monster, huh? Who's a monster?
‎谁是怪兽？
Ooh.
‎把狗还给我
Give me my dog.
‎把狗给我
Give me the dog. Come on.
‎快点
‎过来 宝贝 过来
Come here, baby. Come here. [grunts]
‎在这里和爹地待在一起 好吗？
There. You're gonna stay herewith Daddy. Okay?
‎嗨 爸爸
[girl] Hi, Daddy.
‎嗨 甜心
[Boylan] Hey! Hey, sweetheart.
‎爸爸 我真的需要你辅导我写作文
[girl] Dad, I really needyour help with my report.
‎我读书时语文成绩全是A‎我会帮你写作文的
[Boylan] I was straight A's in English.I'll help you with the paper.
‎太好了 爸爸 你会很快到家吗？
That'd be awesome, Dad.Are you gonna be home soon?
‎回家以后 我先读读你写的东西‎然后我们谈谈
When I get there, I'll read what you haveso far and we'll talk about it.
‎他让所有人尽快去校巴停放场找他
[man] He wants to meet everyoneat the bus yard ASAP.
‎他妈的什么事啊？
-What the fuck is this all about?-[man] Just be there.
‎去就对了
‎好吧
[sighs] All right.
‎甜心 听着 我有一个坏消息
Sweetheart, yeah, listen,I got a little bit of bad news.
‎-爸爸…‎-不
-[girl] Dad---No, it's not... It's nothing.
‎没什么 我只是要耽搁15、20分钟‎我刚刚接了一个电话
I'm gonna be about 15, 20 minutes late.I just got a call.
‎你知道这篇作文很重要‎我需要你再读一次
[girl] You know this report's a big deal.
I need you to read it one more time.
‎听着 关于那本书…
Listen, the thing about the book,
‎你写得很漂亮‎关于黑暗 关于冬季来临
you've written all this beautiful stuffabout the darkness, about winter falling,
‎关于那个地方的黑暗‎芝诺比娅的内心黑暗
about the darkness inside the place,the darkness in Zenobia's heart.
‎就照着这个构思写
Just stay with that idea
‎-一直写下去就行了‎-真的吗？
-and take it all the way through.-Really?
‎我觉得这个构思很不错 真的
[Boylan] I think it's a beautiful idea.I really do.
‎我觉得你应该相信自己
-I think you should have confidence.-[girl] Uh-huh.
‎我看过草稿 给你留了批改意见
Now, I read the first draftand I gave you some notes.
‎但基本上我想说的是
But basically, what I'm tellin' you,you turn that thing in,
‎你把草稿交上去 也许能得个A
you probably get an A on the first draft.
‎好吧 但我知道我…
But I know I'm not--
[tires screech]
‎爸爸 出什么事了？爸爸？
-[whimpering]-Dad, what happened? Dad?
‎爸爸？
Dad!
-[grunting]-[gunshot]
‎爸爸 那是什么声音？
-[Boylan groaning]-[girl] Dad, what was that?
‎爸爸！
-Get the fuck off me! Get the fuck off!-Daddy!
‎滚开！你们知道我是谁吗？
-You know who you're dealing with?-Daddy!
‎你们不能这样对待一名警察
[groans] You can't do this to a cop.
-Dad!-I'm a fuckin' cop.
‎-爸爸！‎-我是他妈的警察！
‎我是他妈的警察！
I'm a fuckin' cop.
[grunts]
‎你告诉了不该告诉的人 混蛋
[man] You talkedto the wrong people, asshole.
‎我什么都没说
I didn't give a fuckin' thing.
‎我什么都没告诉他们 我发誓！
I didn't give 'em anything. I swear.
‎求你了！
Please, God.
[scream echoes]
[sirens blaring]
‎早安 波士顿！‎欢迎来到4月18日
[radio host] Good mornin', Boston.Welcome to April 18th.
‎今天的天气很适合野餐‎难以置信吧？
We're gonna have some picnic weathertoday, can you believe that?
‎最高气温将近20摄氏度‎没错 你没听错
With highs in the upper sixties.
That's right, you heard me.
‎将近20摄氏度
Upper sixties and zero chanceof rain, so pack up the kids,
‎下雨的概率为零
‎带上孩子们 带上三明治
pack up the sandwiches,
‎给自己倒一些柠檬水吧
and pour yourself some luscious lemonade,
‎因为波士顿的春天来了
because it's spring timein Boston, people.
‎让自己度过美好的一天吧
And have yourself a wonderful day.
[man speaking indistinctly over speaker]
‎下一站是第五街 将于五分钟后到站
Next stop is Fifth Street,in five minutes.
‎怎么回事？
[woman] What the hell?
‎特里？
Terry?
‎特伦斯！
Terrence?
‎车怎么了…
What happened to the...
-[screaming]-[tires screeching]
‎特伦斯！
Terrence!
[screaming]
‎天啊！
[crying] Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, somebody help me.
[crying]
‎特伦斯！
Terrence!
Terry!
Are you fuckin' with me? Are you?
[continues crying]
‎嘿
Hey. He snores.
‎他打呼噜
‎这是怎么回事？
What happened here?
‎临别的小礼物
Oh, a little going away present.
‎我给你买了吃的
[Henry] I got groceries for you.
‎别吃冰箱右边的东西 那是霍克的
Don't eat anything on the right sideof the fridge. It belongs to Hawk.
‎你有像样的食物吗？
Aw, do you got any real food?
‎法兰克福香肠是我的‎剩下的是他的
[Henry] Frankfurters are mine.The rest is his.
‎那个大块头呢？
Where's the giant?
‎他五点起床
Gets up at five, starts running.
‎开始跑步
We got no milk.
‎没有牛奶了
‎里面有一些燕麦牛奶‎但那是霍克的
There's some oatmeal milk in there,but it belongs to Hawk.
‎燕麦牛奶？那是什么鬼？
Oat milk? What the fuck is that?
‎天知道 我只知道他整天喝这个
Who knows? All I know ishe drinks it all the time.
‎不知道 胡乱猜猜看‎也许加点水或牛奶什么的
I don't know, Henry. Take a wild guess.
Maybe water or milk or somethin'.
‎加牛奶的话 不如直接用他妈的牛奶
If you put milk in it,you might as well use milk.
‎已经确认 受害者是波士顿警局的‎约翰博伊兰警监
It's been confirmed that the victimis Boston Police Captain John Boylan.
‎非官方消息人士称‎这是一次行刑式谋杀
Unofficial sources have described itas an execution-style killing.
‎目前尚未逮捕任何人
No arrests have been made.
‎见鬼
-Back to you in the studio.-Holy shit.
‎谢谢 目前正在进行全城搜捕…
[reporter 2] Thank you for that.There is a city-wide manhunt...
‎老天爷 有人杀了博伊兰？
Jesus Christ. Somebody killed Boylan?
‎…波士顿将进入警戒状态
‎是你干的吗？
Was it you?
‎…迄今为止对该案守口如瓶
Police are being tight-lippedon the case so far,
‎但目击者称 见到一辆深蓝色的SUV…
but witnesses saythey saw a dark blue SUV...
‎狗杂种 博伊兰终于被干掉了
Son of a bitch,they finally killed Boylan.
‎如果任何人有任何线索‎请联系最近的波士顿警局
[doorbell rings]
‎想猜猜是谁吗？
You wanna guess who that could be?
‎我能看见他们
I can see 'em.
‎-来得够快的‎-是啊
-That's pretty quick, huh?-Yeah.
‎哇
Wow.
‎真是惊喜
Well, this is a surprise.
‎抱歉 斯宾塞 我必须问问你
Yeah. Sorry, Spense, I gotta ask you.
‎昨晚你在哪里？
Where were you last night?
‎你懂的
You know how it is.
‎你出狱的当天晚上‎博伊兰警监就死了
Captain Boylan diesthe same night that you get out.
‎你是头号嫌犯
You're on the top of the suspect list.
‎昨晚他在这里 我看着他上床睡觉的
He was right here. I tucked him in myself.
‎不仅如此 他还有一个室友
Not only that, he's got a roommatethat was sleepin' ten feet away from him.
‎就睡在离他三米远的地方
‎只有一米 亨利 不过多谢了
That's more like three feet,Henry, but thank you very much.
‎好吧 不在场证明是个好东西 走吧
All right.An alibi's a beautiful thing. Let's go.
‎-这就完事了？‎-是的
-[detective] That's it?-Yep.
‎如果最终我觉得是你干的
If it turns out I like you for this,
‎检察官会像戳破气球一样‎戳破这个老家伙的说辞
the DA will pop the old guy's storylike a balloon.
‎约翰博伊兰是个好警察
John Boylan was a good cop.
‎跟博伊兰太太说去吧 现在他死了‎至少她不用守在急诊室
You should tell that to Mrs. Boylan.
At least with him dead,she can stay out of the emergency room.
‎-让我帮你…‎-知道吗 大嘴巴
-Help me help you.-You know what, big mouth?
‎我比你晚两年从警校毕业
I graduated the Academytwo years after you did.
‎我侦办凶杀案
And I work Homicide.
‎我穿西装 佩戴警徽 你算老几？
I wear a suit and carry a gold shield.
Who the hell are you?
‎狗屁不是
-Nothing.-Okay, let's go.
‎-好了 走吧‎-曾经的罪犯
An ex-con. I'm livin' your dream life,you piece of shit.
‎我过着你梦寐以求的生活 王八蛋
‎够了！
[Driscoll] Enough!
‎他有不在场证明
Man's got an alibi. Let's go.
‎走吧
[sighs]
[Driscoll sighs]
‎抱歉 斯宾塞 你是嫌疑人
Sorry, Spense. You're on the list.
‎博伊兰这件事 是个…
This Boylan thing...It's, uh... It's a problem.
‎是个麻烦
‎是个大麻烦 你真走运‎要去亚利桑那了
It's a real problem.You're lucky you're going to Arizona.
‎我真想跟你一起去 妈的
Wish I was goin' with you, man. Shit.
‎替我问候那株仙人掌
Say hi to that cactus for me.
‎上车 老兄 结束了 别闹了
Get in the car, man. It's over. Stop.
‎妈的
Shit.
‎欢迎回家
Welcome home.
‎来吧 我给你做点吃的
Come on, I'll make you somethin'.
‎警察局长约翰博伊兰‎今天清晨被人发现死亡
[host over radio] Police Chief John Boylanwas found dead early this morning,
‎消息人士称‎他死于可怕的行刑式谋杀
in what sources are calling"a gruesome execution-style murder."
‎博伊兰警监已在波士顿警局‎工作了22年
Captain Boylan is a 22-year veteranof the Boston PD.
‎下面是波士顿市长马蒂里昂斯‎刚刚发表的讲话
This, from Boston MayorMarty Langs just moments ago.
‎当一位警官被杀‎他的死是对我们所有人的打击
[mayor] When a police officer gets killed,it's a death that hits us all.
‎我们所有人都失去了一位亲人
It is the death ofa family member for all of us.
‎今天 每一位波士顿市民‎都痛失了一位亲人
Today, every citizen of Bostonhas lost a family member.
‎我们像一家人一样一起哀悼‎我们将治愈…
And we grieve together as a family.
-We will heal---[turns radio off]
‎（贝蒂卡车驾校）
‎嘿 等一下 说你呢！
[Betty] Hey! Wait! You!
‎你是怎么搞的？
What the hell's the matter with you?Can't you read?
‎你不识字吗？
‎哦 对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
‎你是来学车的吗？
You here for the school?
‎我没看见告示牌
I didn't see the sign there. Yeah.
‎-好的‎-那儿有告示牌
Well, there's a sign.
‎-你不识字吗？进来‎-好的
-Can't you read? Get in.-Okay. I'm sorry about that.
‎-抱歉‎-嗯
-Yeah.-Beautiful truck.
‎-卡车很漂亮‎-是的 它叫“黑贝蒂”
[Betty] She is. Her name is Black Betty.
‎这门课的第一条规矩是‎把你学过的驾驶卡车的知识
First rule in this classis to take everything you've learned
‎统统冲进马桶里
about being in a four-wheelerand flush it down the toilet.
‎你的手脚要控制一辆‎快速移动的36吨钢铁巨兽
Your hands and feet are in chargeof 80,000 pounds of fast moving steel
‎你必须时刻成为道路上最聪明的人
and you must be the smartest personon the road at all times.
‎你需要保持清醒
You need to be awake,you need to be alert and in charge.
‎你需要保持警惕 掌控局面
‎如果你犯错
You mess up, and a mini-vanwith three sleeping kids,
‎撞上一辆面包车‎车上三个熟睡的孩子会被压成肉饼
and they get flattened like a pancake.
‎现在到处都有摄像头 你绝对逃不掉
And nowadays, there are allthese cameras everywhere.
You're not gonna get away with it.
‎现在开始今天的课程 好吗？
Now let's get to today's lesson, okay?
‎（谁杀了博伊兰？）
[Betty continues speaking indistinctly]
‎有问题吗？
Any questions?
‎（为什么？）
‎有问题吗？
Any questions? Any questions?
[upbeat hip-hop music playing]
‎-嘿 斯宾塞‎-嘿
-Hey, Spenser.-Hey.
‎茜茜打了很多次电话来
Cissy called a bunch of times.
‎-‎多少次？‎-‎22次
-How many times?-Like 22 times.
‎他不在
He's not here.
‎别吊儿郎当了 我想让你看看霍克
Quit fuckin' around.I want you to take a look at Hawk.
[grunting]
‎这孩子的技术比较生疏‎但我认为他很有天分
This kid is raw,but I think he's got a lot of talent.
‎有可能脱颖而出
I think he could be somethin' special.
‎时间到！
-[alarm beeps]-[referee] Time!
‎-你出拳就像个娘们儿‎-你说什么？
-You punch like a bitch.-What the fuck? [yells]
‎-时间到！‎-你再说一次！
-[referee] Hey! Time! Time!-[Hawk] Say that fuckin' shit again!
‎嘿 分开！
Hey, hey! Break it up! Break it up!
‎把他拖出来！
Get him outta there!
‎快把他拖出来！
Get him the hell outta here! Out, out!
‎出来！
[referee] Get him out!
‎放开我
[Hawk] Get the fuck off me, man!
‎嘿
Hey. You're a fighter, all right?
‎你是个拳手 必须要能够控制自己
You gotta be able to control yourself.
‎亨利 这家伙不懂如何出拳
Henry, this guy doesn'teven know how to throw a punch.
‎听到了吗？我一直在跟你说
You hear him?Haven't I been tellin' you that?
‎你不懂如何出拳
That you don't knowhow to throw a punch?
‎信不信我踢你的…
[Hawk] How about I kick youin the fuckin'--
‎学会出拳以前 不许踢人
There'll be no kickingtill you learn how to punch.
‎他来教你
He's gonna teach you.
‎我不工作
-[Spenser] I'm not workin' with him.-[Henry] Yeah, you are.
‎-不 你要工作‎-我不
-[Spenser] I'm not. No.-[Henry] You are.
‎-你要！‎-不！
‎-我希望你教他‎-我不干
-I want you to work with me.-I'm not doing it.
‎-我在求你‎-我不管
-I'm asking you to do it.-I don't give a shit.
‎一、二
One, two.
‎嘿 出拳就行了 双脚别动
Hey, hey. Just punch, all right?
Keep your feet on the ground.
‎来一记勾拳让我看看
Throw a hook. Let me see a hook.
‎上勾拳
Uppercut.
‎停
Dude, stop, stop.
‎髋部 要转动髋部才行
Hips. You gotta turn the hips,all right? Turn the hips.
‎懂吗？转动髋部
‎砰 转动
Boom. Turn, turn, turn.
‎转动
-Turn. Turn.-Like that?
‎-像这样？‎-对
‎要将对手打倒 不需要用蛮力
Yeah. You don't need muscleto knock somebody out.
‎他在哪儿？
[Cissy] Where is he?
["Mississippi Queen" playing]
♪ Mississippi Queen ♪
‎惨了
Oh, shit.
‎我等了这么久 却只能来这里找你？
I waited all this time.I gotta come find you here?
‎不行 我来说 你好好听着
[Cissy] No. I'm gonna talk,you are gonna listen.
‎-别再逼我倒退了 我不喜欢…‎-你不喜欢？
-Don't keep backin' me up, okay? I...-You don't like it?
‎-你不喜欢这种感觉？‎-听着 别闹了
-You don't like the way this feels?-Cut the shit.
‎-你搞什么？‎-知道我怎么想吗？
-You know what I think?-[Spenser] What?
‎你太喜欢拳击台了 所以跑来这里
I think you like it in thereso much, you come here.
‎一群大男人像他妈的大猩猩一样‎相互扇耳光、挠痒痒
Bunch of grown men slappin' and ticklin'each other like fuckin' gorillas.
‎我是来工作的 好吗？‎我想过上更好的生活 仅此而已
I'm in here working.I'm tryin' to better my life. That's it.
‎我以为你把我忘了
‎你在坐牢！
You were in prison!
‎-我该怎么做？等你吗？‎-对啊
-What was I supposed to do? Wait?-Yeah.
‎连婚戒都没有？
With no ring?
‎每周跑去看你 聊些引人入胜的话题
Goin' up there every weekso we could have riveting conversations,
‎翻什么篇 我那只是在过日子而已
What you're calling "move on"is me just living.
‎我是个非常成功的…
I am a very successful--
‎-继续转动髋部 兄弟‎-看着我 我在说话呢
-Keep turning your hips, bro.-Look at me when I'm talking to you.
‎我是个非常成功的小企业主
I'm a very successfulsmall business owner.
‎很多人排着长队想跟我合作
People line up aroundthe block to work with me.
‎我的宠物生意很赚钱‎所有人都想跟我…
I got poodles comin' out of my ass.Everybody wants to work--
‎抱歉 戴维斯小姐 斯宾斯正在工作
[over speakers] Excuse me,Miss Davis. Spenser's working.
‎能不能改天再找他谈？
Maybe you could talk to him later?
‎-你现在成了他的保镖了吗 亨利？‎-没关系 亨利
-What? Are you his bodyguard now?-It's okay.
‎看着我 行吗？
Look, look. Look at me.Look at me. Listen, okay?
‎对不起
I'm sorry. All right? I am. I mean it.
‎好吗？我真的很抱歉
‎你无法建立真正的亲密关系
You are incapable of real intimacy.
‎我是来告诉你
And I came here to tell youI never wanna see you again.
‎我再也不想见到你
[mouthing] Bye. All right.
‎能量进 能量出
[Hawk] Energy in, energy out.
[chanting]
‎现在插播一条快讯
[TV playing indistinctly]
‎-亨利 他是个怪咖‎-谢了
[Spenser] Henry?He's a very strange person.
‎是波士顿警局的警探特伦斯格林汉
as Boston Police DetectiveTerrence Graham.
‎谢谢 据我了解‎格林汉是波士顿警局的
[news anchor] Thank you. I understandGraham is now the lead suspect
‎约翰博伊兰警监被害案的‎头号嫌疑人
in the murder case ofBoston Police Captain John Boylan.
‎我认识那孩子
I know that kid.
‎特伦斯格林汉死于枪击
[reporter] Terrence Graham'sdeath was by gunshot
‎我们听说他是开枪自杀
and we're hearing thatthat gunshot was self-inflicted.
‎-尸体被发现时…‎-不可能
There's no way.
‎这是个好孩子 亨利 洁身自好
This kid was a good kid, Henry. Clean.
‎我和他一起接受过战术训练
I was in tactical training with him.
‎我从没见过像他这样快乐的人
I've never seen somebody as happy as him.
‎已婚
Married, pregnant wife.
‎妻子怀孕了
‎他绝不可能自杀
There's no way he's taking his own life.
‎格林汉在禁毒科工作‎与约翰博伊兰警监是同事
[reporter] Graham worked in the narcoticsdivision with Captain John Boylan
‎就在几小时前 有人在南波士顿的‎校巴停放场发现了约翰的尸体
who, just hours before,was found dead in a South Boston bus yard.
‎警方认为特伦斯格林汉‎恶意杀害了博伊兰警监
[news anchor] Now,police believe Terrence Graham
‎认定这是杀人后自杀
viciously murdered Captain Boylanand are calling it a murder-suicide.
‎太黑暗了
That's dark.
‎有什么关系？‎你要去亚利桑那开卡车了
Ah, what the hell difference does it make?
You're gonna be in Arizona,drivin' a truck.
‎没错 亨利
That's right, Henry.It's none of my business.
‎不关我的事
‎格林汉警官死后 留下了‎他的妻子乐迪莎和儿子罗兰
Officer Graham is survivedby his wife Letitia and their son Rowan.
‎你说的不是真的！
What you're saying is not true!Terrence was a good policeman!
‎特伦斯是个好警察！
‎为什么没有人知道真相？
[crying] Why doesn't anyone knowwhat's happening?
‎他是个好丈夫 是个好父亲！
He was a good husband!He was a good father!
‎这是怎么回事？
What's going on?Tell me what's really happening!
‎-告诉我真相！‎-不要 斯宾塞
[Henry] Don't do it, Spense.
‎别管了 离远点
-[Letitia] Don't tell me to calm down!-[Henry] Let it go. Walk away.
‎为什么？
Why? Why? Why? Why?
‎格林汉太太
Mrs. Graham?
Mrs. Graham!
‎嘿 抱歉 我不是故意要吓你
Hey. Sorry...No, I didn't mean to scare you.
‎-你想干嘛？‎-抱歉 我…
-What do you want?-Sorry about that. I, uh...
‎听着
Look... [sighs]
‎我是…
I was, um... I was a friend of Terrence.
‎我是特伦斯的朋友
‎我只想跟你聊一下
I just wanted to talk to you for a minute.
‎你是谁？
Who are you?
‎我叫斯宾塞‎不知道特伦斯有没有跟你提起过我
Uh, my name is Spenser. I don't knowif Terrence told you about me.
‎几年前 我和约翰博伊兰起了冲突
Um, I got into a situationyears ago with John Boylan.
‎为此坐了很长时间的牢
It sent me to prison for quite some time.
‎是你？
That was you?
‎嗯 我只是觉得…
Yeah. I just thought maybeI could help you in some way.
‎也许我可以帮到你
‎怎么帮？
Help, how?
‎查明真相
Uh, I don't know, find the truth?
‎你丈夫跟博伊兰之间有矛盾吗？
Did your husbandhave any problems with Boylan?
‎特里觉得…
[chuckles] Terry thoughtBoylan was a loudmouth
‎博伊兰喜欢吹嘘 自命不凡
whose ego could fill a room.
‎你知道
You know, old school,
‎喜欢炫耀权力‎凌驾于法律之上的老派警察
above the law copwho liked to flaunt his power.
‎没错 博伊兰就是这种人
Yeah, that's Boylan to a T.
‎博伊兰管特伦斯叫“辅祭男童”
[sighs] Boylan called Terrence"altar boy." [chuckles]
‎特伦斯是否懂得相关技术‎能让汽车的安全气囊失效？
Did Terrence have the technical knowledgeto disable the airbag in your vehicle?
‎干嘛问这个？
Why?
‎因为不让安全气囊失效‎就无法用这辆车撞人
Well, because you can't use a vehicle asa ram unless you can disable the airbags.
‎他们没问我这个问题
Mmm-mmm. They didn't ask me that.Why didn't they ask me that?
‎-他们为什么不问？‎-因为他们已经知道答案了
Because they already know the answer.
‎他们在我们家找到了毒品！
They found drugs in our home.
‎说他贩毒
‎-检查这堵墙‎-他们直奔藏毒品的地方
[Letitia] They went right up to it.
‎你的丈夫在贩卖毒品
Your husband was dealing narcotics.
‎他们说可以定我共谋罪！
[Letitia crying] And they saidthey could pin me for conspiracy
‎并把我的儿子带走
and take my boy away.
‎相信他们 好吗？‎他们有这个能力 也会这样做
Well, believe them, okay?They can and they will.
‎你最后一次见到你丈夫是什么时候？
When is the last timeyou saw your husband?
‎前一天晚上
The night before?
‎特伦斯说要去见他的搭档
Terrence said he had to meet his partner.
‎斯科特特雷勒
Um, Scott Traylor?
‎他们去了一家…
And they... They went to some cop bar.
‎警察聚会的酒吧
‎“干杯”酒吧？
Sláinte?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎我认识斯科特特雷勒
I know who Scott Traylor is.
‎我会尽力去查 看看是否有帮助
I'll dig up anything I can,see if it helps.
‎你是…
[breathes shakily] And this...
‎你是为了报仇吗？
-This revenge for you?-No.
‎不是
‎我妈妈生前也很不幸
My mom wasn't dealt a good hand either.
‎但是她勇猛、坚强
But she was fierce, tough,and she had a lot of heart.
‎她充满勇气
‎我有很多缺点 格林汉太太‎相信我 很多
I got a lot of flaws, Mrs. Graham.Believe me, a lot.
‎但我的所有优点都来自她
But anything I got good in me,it came from her.
‎听起来她是个好女人
Sounds like she was a good woman.
‎好好照顾你的儿子
Keep an eye on your son.I'll be in touch, okay?
‎我们再联系 好吗？
‎（“干杯”酒吧）
[crowd on TVsinging "Sweet Caroline"]
♪ Sweet Caroline, pa, pa, pa ♪
♪ Good times never seemed so good ♪
♪ So good, so good ♪
-["Sweet Caroline" continues playing]-[indistinct chatter]
[Spenser] Hmm.
‎你是特伦斯格林汉的搭档‎斯科特特雷勒吧？
You Scotty Traylor?Terrence Graham's partner?
‎你是谁？
Who are you?
‎我知道特伦斯是被他们诬陷的
I know Terrence didn't dowhat they're pinning on him.
‎我去撒尿
I'm gonna go take a piss. Come see me.
‎来找我
[music continues playing faintly]
‎我想起来你是谁了
You know, it hit me who you are.
‎你被关进监狱时‎这间酒吧有很多人举杯庆祝
A lot of guys in this bar,they celebrated when you got locked up.
‎你我都知道 特伦斯不是个黑警察
You and I both knowTerrence was not a crooked cop.
‎博伊兰被杀那晚 他在这间酒吧吗？
Was he in this barthe night Boylan was killed, yes or no?
‎在
[sighs] Yes.
‎他是否怀疑博伊兰是个黑警察？
And did he suspect Boylanof bein' a dirty cop?
[sighs]
Huh?
‎难以置信
Unbelievable. How was Walpole?
‎在监狱里过得怎么样？‎是不是千辛万苦才出来？
Did you work your way right upto the honeymoon suite?
‎哇 巡警麦克林
Wow, Patrolman Macklin.
‎才走了50步‎听到你们喘气的声音有多粗了吗？
Hear how heavy you guysare breathin' from walkin' 50 steps?
‎你来这里干什么？
What the hell are you doin' here?
‎这个酒吧不接待童子军
This isn't a bar for boy scouts.
‎我跟这个最近死了搭档的年轻人
Well, I said somethinginsensitive to this young man
‎说了些不识趣的话
who recently lost his partner
‎你们救了我 让我免于挨揍 谢了
and I think you guys just saved mean ass kicking, so thank you.
‎他什么都没做 他道歉了
He didn't do nothin'. He apologized.
‎是吗？
Yeah? Did you apologizefor beatin' down your own captain?
‎你是因为打了你的警监而道歉吗？
‎我一直没机会道歉
[Spenser] I never got the chance.
‎老天爷
[Macklin] Jesus Christ.
‎你真有种
The set of balls on you.
‎不知道你注意到没有
I don't know if you noticed it,but it's Sergeant Macklin now.
‎我现在是警长了
‎哇
Wow. [chuckling]For you to be a sergeant,
‎你都能当上警长
‎你的上司都死绝了吧？
I'd say all your superiorsmust be dead, no?
‎那不可能 对吧？‎所以是怎么回事？文员弄错了吗？
That's impossible. So, what was it?
‎天啊 你果然是个混蛋
Jesus, you are a prick.
‎谢谢
Thank you. [groans]
-[groans]-[Macklin chuckles]
‎混…
Aah! Bad mother...
‎打得好
[breathes deeply] Oh, that was good.
That was good. That was real good.
["Sweet Caroline"continues playing]
‎我们让他闭嘴
[cop 1] We're gonna cut those out.
‎把这个混蛋交给我
[cop 2] Give me that asshole.
[yells]
‎妈的！操
Shit! Fuck.
[groans]
‎嘿 混蛋
[Macklin] Hey, asshole.
‎滚出马萨诸塞州
Get the fuck out of Massachusetts.
‎听到了吗 斯宾塞？
You fuckin' hear me, Spenser? You're done.
‎你玩完了
‎再见
See you later.
[door chimes]
‎借你的厕所用用
-I need to use your bathroom.-Customers only.
‎仅供顾客使用
‎好吧
Fine. Here.
‎拿去
‎现在我算顾客了吧？把钥匙给我
Now it's official. Give me the key.
‎那边 走到头右转
There. It's down the hall, to the right.
‎找到了
[Spenser] Bingo.
‎老兄 你不能来后面 你他妈的干嘛？
[cashier] Dude, you can't be back here!What are you doing?
‎我只是需要那天的监控录像带
I just need the tape from your cameras.From the other day.
‎这不是录像带
Oh, it's not a tape.
‎嗯 我需要这块硬盘！
Well, I need this hard drive!
‎那是电视盒
That's the cable box.
‎-什么？‎-那是电视盒
-What?-That's the cable box.
‎在云端
They're in the cloud.
‎云端是什么鬼？
What the fuck is a cloud?
‎-就是云端‎-听着 老兄
-The cloud. Yeah...-Listen, dude...
‎把云端交出来
-[grunts]-[woman gasps]
‎我还以为你知道如何出拳呢
Ooh, I thought you knew how to punch.
‎他们有四个人
-There was four of them. Okay?-You good?
‎-懂吗？‎-你没事吧？
Sit down, will you?
‎来吧 拜托
Come on, please.
‎谢了
-Thank you.-[typing]
‎好 让我看看右上角的摄像头
Let me look at the top right camera.
‎那是特伦斯·格林汉的车‎用来谋杀博伊兰的那辆
That's Terrence Graham's car.It was used in the Boylan hit.
‎我们来看看他出来后发生了什么
Let's see what happens when he comes out.
‎他出来了
There he is.
‎好 等一下
All right, hold on.
‎你要去见谁 特伦斯？
Who are you meeting, Terrence?
‎那是一辆科尔维特Z06
[Hawk] That's a Corvette Z06.
‎可以放大点吗？
[Spenser] Can you zoom in a little bit?
‎太模糊了 妈的
It's too blurry. Shit!
‎你要找的是一个肥胖的白人老家伙
It means you're lookingfor a fat, old, white dude
‎-离过三次婚 鸡巴很小‎-为什么这么说？
with three divorces and a micro-dick.
[Spenser] Why's that?
‎还有谁会开那样一辆科尔维特
Who else you think drivesa Corvette like that?
‎回到另一个摄像头
Go back to the other camera.Now, fast forward.
‎快进
‎等一下
Wait, wait, wait. Zoom in a little more.
‎再放大一点
‎让我看看
Let me see.
‎他们是一起离开的
So, they all left together.
‎知道这些人是谁吗？
[Hawk] You got any ideawho those guys are?
‎不知道
[Spenser] I don't know,but I know where they went.
‎但我知道他们去哪儿了
‎一、二 上勾拳
[trainer] One, two, uppercut.One, two! One, two!
‎一、二 快点
‎站稳 移动
Come on! Stick and move.Stick and move. Stick and move.
‎一、二
One, two, one, two.
‎就这样 移动
That's it. Move, move it.That's it. Come on.
‎很好
‎来吧
Punch it.
‎斯宾塞 你怎么来了？
[exhales] Spenser!What the hell are you doing here?
‎你想离开西莫利的健身馆吗？
You thinkin' of leavin' Cimoli's?
‎不 我想问你几个‎关于特伦斯格林汉的问题
No, look, I wanted to ask youa few questions about Terrence Graham.
‎你觉不觉得他的案子有古怪？
Man, anything seem off to you about it?
‎觉得
Yeah. The fact thatyou're askin' me about it.
‎你来问我这个就很古怪
‎你现在成了私家侦探了吗？
What are you,a private detective now, huh?
‎是这么回事吗？
Is that what's goin' on here?
‎我记得有犯罪前科的人申请不到执照
'Cause I was under the impression that
-a convicted felon can't get a license.-[chuckles]
‎凭你的人脉 没准儿我能得到赦免
With your connections,I could probably get a pardon.
[laughing]
‎听着 别趟这个浑水
Listen, let this one go.
‎格林汉手脚不干净 他家里藏有毒品
Graham's dirty, drugs in his house.
‎听着 他们说博伊兰‎是在一个校车停放场遇害的 对吧？
Look, they said that Boylanwas killed in the school bus yard, right?
‎还说特伦斯格林汉‎先用他的SUV撞了他
And that Terrence Grahamrammed him first with his SUV?
‎他就是这样先发制人的
That's how he got the drop on him.
‎嗯 但警方在他家的外面‎找到了他的SUV
Yeah, but they found his SUVoutside of his house.
‎他开车回家 开枪自杀‎就算不是福尔摩斯…
Then he drove himself homeand blew his brains out.
You don't haveto be Sherlock Holmes here--
‎他肯定是让安全气囊失效了
Well, he must've disabled 'em.
‎但是说不通啊‎何必大老远地开车回家…
Yeah, but it doesn't add up.Why drive all the way home?
‎开枪自杀呢？
To shoot himself?
‎就不怕他的孩子走出来‎看见他死在车里吗？
Run the risk of his kid walkin' outand seein' him dead in the car?
‎斯宾塞
Spenser, the man was notin his right mind.
‎那家伙精神不正常
‎那犯罪现场呢？
And what about the crime scene?
‎没有任何异常 对吧？
Everything added up, right?
‎你把我问住了 我没去现场
Beats me. I haven't been there.
‎你现在回家了 亲爱的 别管了
You're home, baby.Let it go. Let it go, man.
‎别管了 那只会给你带来伤痛‎痛苦和挫败感
The only thing that it's gonna bring youis grief, pain, frustration.
‎我还要回去工作呢 我已经不年轻了
I gotta get back to work,I ain't gettin' no younger.
‎好吧 他说得对 我的右手放得太低了
All right. He's right,I'm keepin' my right hand too low.
‎一、二 来啊
One, two! One, two!
‎针对震惊波士顿全城的‎凶残的双重谋杀案
[reporter] Investigationinto the brutal double homicide
‎今天调查仍在继续
that has rocked the cityof Boston continues today.
‎我们从波士顿警局内部人士那里获悉
We're hearing insidethe Boston Police Department,
‎特伦斯格林汉警官将博伊兰警监
that Officer Terrence Grahamlured Captain Boylan
‎引诱到一处偏僻的城市校车停放场
to an isolated city school bus yardwhere he killed him violently.
‎然后残忍地杀害了他
‎据说特伦斯格林汉是唯一的嫌疑人
It is believed Terrence Grahamis the only suspect.
‎你要学会移动 懂吗？
‎有时候防守是最好的进攻 来吧
Defense is the best offense sometimes. Go.
‎非常完美
[Spenser] That's pretty perfect.
‎我有机会驾驶黑贝蒂吗？
Do I get a shotat drivin' the Black Betty?
‎你还没准备好 斯宾塞先生
You're not ready, Mr. Spenser.
‎那辆卡车太漂亮了
Well, uh, she sure is a pretty truck.
‎这就对了 很好
-[breathes heavily]-[Spenser] There you go.
‎就像这样
Yeah. Okay. Get in.
[breathes heavily]
‎格挡 很好
Now, block. Good.
‎格挡
-[exhales]-And block, block, block.
‎格挡 看到了吗？
-Oh, you see that?-Yeah.
‎-嗯‎-你没挡住
You have to listen. All right? Yeah.
‎-像这样？‎-对
‎市府官员打算用一场葬礼‎表达对博伊兰警监的敬意
[reporter] City officialsare planning a funeral
to honor the fallen Captain Boylan
‎很快就会公布细节
and will announce details shortly.
‎（德里斯科撒谎）
‎干得漂亮
[Spenser] Good job.
‎我去买点吃的 你要吗？
I'm gonna go get somethin' to eat.You want somethin'?
‎（有机咖啡厅）
‎谢谢
-Thank you.-For what?
‎-谢我什么？‎-教我拳击 你说得对 我需要指导
The boxing. You're right, I need it.
‎我只是受亨利所托
I'm just doin' what Henry asked me to do.
‎这位先生的绿色女神
Got one Green Goddess for the gentleman.
‎你会很喜欢这个的‎比监狱伙食好多了 我保证
Gonna like this a lot more thanprison food, I guarantee you.
‎那可不一定
I don't know about that.What'd you go up for?
‎你是怎么进去的？
‎过失杀人
Manslaughter.
‎从一级谋杀减下来的
Reduced from murder one.
‎蹲了四年 因为表现良好提前出狱
Served four years, out on good behavior.
‎现在 多亏了亨利 我正在改变人生
And now, thanks to Henry,I'm changin' my life.
‎-是吗？‎-嗯
-Really?-Yeah.
like my dad would've wanted.
‎你老爸？
Your dad, huh?
‎他什么样？
What was he like?
‎他是个好人
He was a good guy. Military man, pilot.
‎军人 飞行员
‎善于为人处世
Man of the world type, you know?
‎我们搬过很多次家
We moved around a lot.Settled in New Orleans.
‎最后在新奥尔良定居下来
‎他目睹了一些…
He witnessed some realmessed up shit in our community.
‎我们社区的不平事
‎所有人都叫他装作没看见
Everybody told him to look the other way.
‎但他做不到
He couldn't.
‎他死了
He died, a hero.
‎像个英雄
‎不肯少管闲事
Not minding his own business.
‎怎么死的？
And what happened?
‎我不想跟你谈这件事‎也许永远都不会
I'm not gonna get into that, not with you.
‎好吧
-Probably not ever, actually.-Fair enough.
‎好了 我去洗手
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
‎好吧 随便你
[Cissy] It's fine. Whatever you want.
‎冷静 放松
[man] Yeah, chill out. Relax.
‎嘿 你干什么？
Hey, what are you doin'?
‎你他妈的跟踪我？
You followin' me?
‎是我先进厕所的
Uh, I came to the bathroom first.
‎你跟着我来的
You followed me in here.So, you're following me.
‎所以是你在跟踪我
‎你来这家餐厅干什么？
What are you doin' in this restaurant?
‎听着 不要无理取闹 行吗？
-Don't be ridiculous, okay?-Don't be ridiculous.
‎-无理取闹‎-你干什么？
-What are you doing?-What are you doing?
‎-你干什么？‎-不要
-Don't! You know what? You...-What?
‎-什么？‎-知道吗？你…
‎我们今天…
We're not doing... [sighs]
‎-我们今天不能这样‎-不能哪样？
-We're not doing this today.-We're not doin' what?
‎我们出去吧
Oh, we're just gonna go.
‎现在是你在推我
-[Spenser] Stop that.-You're the one pushin' me.
‎怎么 你是管锁的警察吗？
What are you, the lock police?
‎好吧 你很漂亮 你想让我干嘛？
All right, you look good.What do you want from me?
‎我想让你干很多事‎因为你猜怎么着 你也很帅
I want a lot from you,'cause guess what? You look good, too.
‎-是吗？这样如何？喜欢吗？‎-不许碰我的头发
How about this?Huh? You like this?
‎-我知道你喜欢什么‎-好啊 展示一下？
-I know what you like. Come here.-You wanna show me?
‎好
-Yes? All right.-Yeah. All right. I got you.
[Cissy moans] Stop, stop.
[breathes heavily]
‎-喜欢吗？‎-喜欢
-Yeah?-Yeah.
-Like that?-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [moans]
‎好爽！
[both breathing heavily]
‎哦 见鬼 好的！
Oh, shit! Okay! Okay! Okay! [grunts]
‎我看你敢
Don't you dare! Don't you dare!
‎不许比我先高潮 知道吗？
Don't you darefuckin' cum before me. Okay?
[mouths] Fuck yeah.
‎每次都是茜茜先高潮！
Cissy always finishes first!
‎用力操我！
[moans] Fuck me harder!
‎操！
-Fuck! Fuck!-Was that it?
‎-抱歉‎-操！红袜队加油！
Go, Sox!
‎红袜队加油！
Don't stop! Don't stop!
‎-红袜队加油！‎-见鬼！
-Don't stop!-Oh, shit!
‎-他妈的老天爷！‎-闭嘴！
-Oh, my fuckin' God!-Shut up!
‎他妈的老天爷！
Oh, my fuckin' God!
-[moans]-[both panting]
‎我们现在处于窗口期 斯宾塞
We're in the window right now, Spenser.
‎什么窗口期？
-What's that?-Remember the window?
‎还记得窗口期吗？
‎你是说我们做完爱后‎五分钟的停战时间？
You mean the five minutesof peace between us
right after we have sex? Yeah.
‎-是啊‎-和我们做爱的时间差不多长
Yeah, lasts about as long as sex with you.
‎-下去‎-好
-Get off me.-Yeah.
[sighs]
‎以前这是我一天中最喜欢的时间‎比做爱还要爽
Used to be my favorite part of the day.
Even better than fuckin'. [sniffles]
‎刚才你似乎很享受
Well, you seem like you liked it.
‎怎么？想再来一次？
-What, you wanna go again?-[toilet flushes]
[sighs]
‎那次我们以为我怀孕了…
That time we thought I was pregnant.
‎还记得你跟我说的话吗？
-Do you remember what you said to me?-Um, I remember the gist.
‎我大概记得
‎你说：
You said,
‎“我不会和你谈婚论嫁
"I'm not sayin' we're gettin' married,
‎但我不会让孩子从小就没有爹”
but that kid's not gonnabe raised without a father."
‎还记得吗？
You remember that?
‎结果是虚惊一场 谢天谢地
It was a false alarm, thank God.
‎但你打算做正确的事 你总是有一种…
But you were gonna do what was right.
‎强烈的道德感
You always had that strong moral code.
‎我要搬去亚利桑那
I'm movin' to Arizona.
‎从头来过
I'm gonna start over. Start fresh.
‎重新开始
‎我从没听过这么蠢的事‎你的家在这里
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
This is your home.
‎除非地狱结冰 不然你别想再碰我
[sighs] Hell will freeze overbefore you ever touch me again.
[door opens]
‎你的裙子…
You got, um... You got a littlestain on your dress there.
‎你的裙子弄脏了一小块
‎就想告诉你一声
Just sayin'.
‎留做纪念
Souvenir.
[sighs] Fuckin'...
-[truck horn blows]-[engine revs]
[rock music playing over car stereo]
‎刚才玩得爽吧？
-[Hawk] You enjoy yourself in there?-Mind your business.
‎嘿 管好你自己的事
‎好的 我管好自己的事
Okay. I'll mind my business.
‎那辆黄色科尔维特算我的事吗？
Is that yellow Corvette my business?
‎见鬼！
Shit!
[tires screeching]
[car engine revving]
[grunts]
‎哇！
-[dog barking]-Whoa!
[dog whimpers and barks]
‎站住 别过来！
[growling]
‎见鬼！
-[barking]-Oh, shit!
[grunts]
[dog growls]
‎妈的！
Fuck! [screams]
‎老天！滚开！
Oh, God! Get the fuck--
[dog snarling]
[screams]
[grunting]
[grunts]
‎妈的 老天！
Fuck off! God!
Oh, my God! [screams]
-[rips]-[whimpers]
[snarling]
[barking]
[yelps]
[groans]
‎该死的王八蛋
[panting] You fuckin' motherfucker...
‎干嘛？
-What?-[barks]
‎见鬼 妈的！
Oh, shit! Fuck!
[grunts]
‎操！
-Fuck!-[snarling]
‎嘿 你在对我的狗干什么？
Hey! What are you doing to my dog?
-[growling]-[whimpering]
‎放开我的狗！
[man] Get off my dog!
‎乐高！
Lego. Come here, Lego.
‎过来 乐高
‎-好姑娘 乖狗狗‎-操
-Good girl. Oh...-Fuck!
‎过来 好姑娘 很好
Come here. Good girl.
‎好姑娘
-Good girl. Aw.-[dog whining]
‎你最好把那条杂种阉了
You better neuter that mutt!
‎滚吧 快滚！
[man] Fuck outta here! Get outta here!
["Willin'" playing]
[exhales] Shit.
♪ I been warped by the rainDriven by the snow ♪
♪ I'm drunk and dirty, don't you know ♪
♪ And I'm still ♪
[over speakers] ♪ Willin' ♪
♪ And I was out on the roadLate at night ♪
[men grunting]
[thudding]
[man] Yes, do it again.
[timer beeping]
-[grunting]-[body thuds]
‎嘿
Hey.
‎多谢你刚才见死不救
Thanks for havin' my back out there.
‎那我该怎么做？
What was I supposed to do?I got my own problems.
‎我自己还麻烦缠身呢
‎知道吗？特伦斯格林汉的儿子‎将失去父亲的陪伴
You know Terrence Graham's son'sgonna grow up without a father?
‎更糟的是
Huh? And worse than that,
‎这个城市的每个人都认为他是个人渣
every single person in this citythinks he died a scumbag.
‎他怎么办？
What about him?
‎你不想帮他洗刷罪名吗？
You don't care about clearin' his name?
Huh?
‎你真可耻
Shame on you.
‎89053QG
8-9-0-5-3-Q-G.
‎什么？
What?
‎89053QG
8-9-0-5-3-Q-G.
‎你看到车牌号了？
You got the license plate?
‎你就不能早点告诉我
You couldn't have yelled that to me
‎省得我被狼狗咬吗？
and prevented mefrom gettin' mauled by a wolf?
‎你是爱狗人士嘛
Yeah, well, you're a dog lover.
‎很好
That's pretty good. Thank you.
‎谢谢
♪ I'll be willin' ♪
♪ To be movin' ♪
‎请42号前往五号柜台办理业务
-[announcer on PA] Now serving 42...-[woman] Next.
...at counter number five.
‎我想不考试就买一本A级驾照
I'd like to buy a Class A licensewithout takin' the test.
‎还有 能不能帮我销几条酒驾记录？
And could you clear a coupleof DUIs off my record, please?
‎你来干什么？
-What are you doin' here?-Aw, hey, Billy.
‎嘿 比利
‎我想找我的登记局线人帮个忙
I need my registeredsnitch to do me a favor.
‎帮我查一个车牌行吗？
Check me a plate, will ya?
‎你已经不是警察了 斯宾塞
-You're not a cop anymore, Spenser.-That's interesting.
‎有意思
‎我需要续领‎我已故母亲的残疾人停车证
[loudly] I need to renew my dead mother'shandicapped parking permit.
‎小点声
[softly] Keep your voice down.
‎还记得上次我私下塞给你500美元‎你帮我销掉醉驾记录吗？
And you know how the last timeI gave you $500 under the table
and you wiped those DUIs off my record?
‎-我又有醉驾记录了‎-够了 好吧
-I got another one.-Fine. Enough.
‎-你要的钱我装在信封里了‎-把车牌号给我
I have the money you requestedin the envelope.
Give me the plate.
‎别这样 老兄
Come on, buddy. You look good.
‎-你气色不错‎-你看着像是睡了一头山地狮
You look like you banged a mountain lion.
‎你看 这就是你需要的文件
As you can see, this is the documentationyou're gonna need.
‎嗯 我看到了 我知道他是谁
I got it. I know who he is.
‎请57号办理业务
[announcer over PA] Now serving 57.
‎谢谢
-Thank you.-At counter number five.
‎霍克
‎（巴黎美甲店）
‎对 就是这里
Oh, right there.
‎滚…
You... can... just...
‎你妈的…
‎蛋
fuck... off.
‎“运动哥”查理本特伍德
[Spenser] Tracksuit Charlie Bentwood.
‎以前是爱尔兰黑帮的
Irish mob throwback.
‎当时爱尔兰黑帮不止存在于烂片之中
Back when the Irish mob existedoutside all those shitty movies.
‎我看看
[Bentwood] There we go.
‎很好
Nice.
‎我想你该告诉我这究竟是怎么回事了
I think it's time you tell mewhat's really goin' on here.
‎曾经有个姑娘 叫做…
There was a girl named Gloria Weisnewski.
‎格洛莉娅维希涅夫斯基
‎她妈妈住在南波士顿‎我经常帮她铲门前的雪
I used to shovel snow offher mother's porch in Southie.
‎她是个聪明的孩子 我看着她长大
She was a smart kid.I watched her grow up.
‎后来开发商来到南波士顿‎大肆修建高档社区
When developers came to Southie,
‎想要摧毁这座城市的灵魂
gentrifying and trying to destroythe soul of the city,
‎她无法视而不见
she couldn't look the other way.
‎我们不能继续…
We can keep on marching!
‎和魔鬼做交易 魔鬼不做交易
[chanting indistinctly]
‎“运动哥”是怎么回事？
Where does Tracksuit Charlie come in?
‎“运动哥”查理一直是‎一个接受雇佣的打手
Tracksuit Charlie wasand is a goon for hire.
‎有人花钱请他骚扰格洛莉娅‎逼她放弃
Somebody paid him to harass Gloria,get her to give up.
‎你给我闭嘴！
-You shut your mouth!-[Gloria shouting indistinctly]
‎把你的脏手拿开
Get your filthy,stinkin' hands out my face!
‎你给我闭嘴 不然我帮你闭嘴
Shut your mouth or I'll shut it for you!
‎然后手段升级了
Then it escalated.
‎打电话
Phone calls, threats, harassment.
‎恐吓
‎骚扰
‎有一天 格洛莉娅回家时‎发现她的猫被钉死在门上
Next thing you know, Gloria comes homeand finds her cat nailed to the door.
[gasps]
‎就算不是天才也知道‎是“运动哥”查理杀了格洛莉娅的猫
It didn't take a genius to know
that it was Tracksuit Charliethat killed Gloria's cat.
‎几周后 我奉命出勤
Couple of weeks later,I was out on a call.
‎坎伯兰农场的经理…
Manager at Cumberland Farms
‎在停车场发现一辆可疑的车辆
had a suspicious vehiclein the parking lot.
‎警方发现后备箱有血液渗出
There was blood leaking from the trunk.
‎我们发现一具…
[inhales sharply] We got a...
I had to tell her mother.
‎不得不告诉她妈妈
‎这比发现尸体更让人不好受
It was almost worse than finding the body.
‎有我在
-[woman sobbing]-I got you.
[Spenser sighs]
‎我和这家人关系很好‎她们是诚实的好人
I don't know,I was so close to the family.
‎所以我不断去看望她
They were good, honest people,so I just kept checkin' in.
‎后来案子转到了凶案组
Got handed over to Homicide.
‎但我无法放手
But I couldn't let it go.
‎我在跟进格洛莉娅的案子时
When I followed up on Gloria's case,
‎发现凶案组毫无作为
I found out Homicidewas just sittin' on it.
‎他们甚至还没有盘问“运动哥”查理
They hadn't even questionedTracksuit Charlie.
‎-警督‎-警佐 你来干什么？
-Lieutenant.-Sergeant, what are you doing here?
‎我想应该由我来判断‎怎样做对我最好
I will actually judgewhat's in my best interest
‎你也应该想想 怎样做对自己最好
and you need to start thinkingabout what's your best interest.
‎马上出去 我们正忙着呢
Sergeant, get your ass outta here.You get out of here now.
We're in the middle of something.
‎你们是忙着调查‎格洛莉娅的凶杀案吗？
[Spenser] Are you in the middle ofinvestigating Gloria Weisnewski's murder?
‎你们应该调查‎却被你压下去了 为什么？
'Cause you should be,but you're burying it. Why?
‎我觉得你应该出去‎而且要小心脚下 孩子
I think you should step outsideand mind your step, son.
‎-是吗？‎-是的
-Really?-Yeah, you really do.
‎别碰我 行吗？
‎醒醒吧
-Wake up!-Get out of here.
‎滚出去 把他赶出去
-Get him outta here!-[officer] Let's go.
‎我应该放手的
[Spenser] I should've walked away,but I knew he was covering something up.
‎但我知道他在掩盖一些事
‎滚吧 垃圾
Get out, you piece of shit.
‎然后我接到《环球报》‎一名记者的电话
[Spenser] And then I get a callfrom this reporter at the Globe,
‎他想让我看一盒触目惊心的录像带
and he wants to show methis very graphic tape.
‎凶案组看过这盒录像带吗？
Has Homicide seen this tape?
‎看过 是一个秘书泄露给我的
Yeah, a secretary leaked it to me.
‎是格洛莉娅维希涅夫斯基
It's Gloria Weisnewski.
‎据说这些禽兽属于贩毒黑帮“三圣帮”
Word is, those animals were partof the Trinitario drug gang.
‎他们甚至还没有盘问‎停车场的工作人员
They haven't even questionedthe guys workin' the lot yet.
‎-等一下 什么？‎-想知道他们掩盖的程度吗？
-What?-You wanna hear the extent of the sandbag?
‎《环球报》不肯报道‎他们让我报道别的新闻
Globe's not gonna run it.They're putting me on another story.
‎他们想隐瞒什么？
-So what're they hiding?-I was hoping you could tell me that.
‎我还指望你来告诉我呢
‎太可恶了
This is fucked up, man.
‎肯定是查理指使他们干的
Tracksuit must have put them on it.
‎该死的博伊兰
Fuckin' Boylan.
‎嘿 态度好一点
Hey, one flash behind.
‎态度好点 亲爱的
One flash behind you, baby.
[knocking at door]
‎老天 直接就进屋了 什么问题？
Jesus. Just walk right in. What questions?
‎他给我看了那盒录像带
He showed me the tape.
‎格洛莉娅维希涅夫斯基‎在停车场遇害的录像带
-What tape?-The tape of Gloria Weisnewski
What tape? I don't knowwhat you're talking about.
‎别跟我装傻 约翰
-Don't play stupid with me.-I'm not playing stupid.
‎我没装傻 不许在我家这样跟我讲话
-Not in your own home.-Don't talk to me like that in my house!
‎-你喝醉了吗？‎-这无关紧要
-Are you drunk right now?-It doesn't matter.
‎-现在是周六上午八点‎-你走吧
It's eight o'clock on a Saturday morning.
[Boylan] Move along.
‎滚出我家 他妈的滚出我家
Get the fuck out of our house!
‎你妻子的脸是怎么回事？
What happened to your wife's face, John?
‎你是个肮脏的警察
You're a filthy cop.
‎真他妈可耻！
[Spenser] You're a fuckin' disgrace.You beat that...
‎你殴打那个…
‎该死！
-[grunts]-[Mrs. Boylan] Fuckin' hell!
‎见鬼 斯宾塞！
Shit.
[grunts]
‎放开他 你这个王八蛋！
Get off of him, you son of a bitch.
‎斯宾塞 住手！
[Driscoll] Spense! Stop!Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
‎喂！
[indistinct shouting]
[Mrs. Boylan] Get off of him!
Get off of him!
[Mrs. Boylan grunting]
‎那个混蛋杀了一只猫？
That fucker over there killed a cat?
‎你就记住了那只猫？
So, the cat is what you'retakin' away from all of this?
‎我们这么办
[Spenser] Here's what we're gonna do.
‎我们揭露这件事
We're gonna blow this whole shit open.
‎还特伦斯一个清白 扳倒这些家伙
Clear Terrence's name,take these guys down.
‎-你想加入吗？‎-我已经加入了
-You want in?-Man, I'm already in.
["Beast" playing]
♪ Stand tall for the beast of America ♪
[air hisses]
‎老天爷
[chuckling] Oh, my God!
♪ Keep it real for the peopleWorkin' overtime ♪
♪ They can't stay livingOff the government's dime ♪
♪ Stand tall for the people of America ♪
‎我喜欢这孩子 亨利
-I like this kid, Henry.-[chuckles]
‎喜欢杀猫的王八蛋
[Hawk] Motherfucker wanna kill cats.
♪ Come on now ♪
‎你有何打算？
[Henry] What are you thinking?
‎-你想吃什么？‎-不知道
-What do you wanna eat?-I don't know.
‎噢 好戏开始了
Oh, Jesus.
‎王八蛋！
Son of a bitch!
‎今天就监视到这里吧
I guess that's it for surveillance today?
‎什么？
-What?-[Bentwood] Son of a...
‎走了
Let's go.
♪ Stand tall for the beast of America ♪
♪ Lay down like a naked dead body ♪
♪ Keep it real for the peopleWorkin' overtime ♪
♪ They can't stay livingOff the government's dime ♪
♪ Come on, people ♪
♪ Ha! ♪
‎肥仔出发了
Fat boy's on the move.
♪ Come on, people ♪
♪ Ha! ♪
[camera shutter clicking]
♪ You see ♪
♪ Suppression is a motherfuckin' prison ♪
♪ So I hand you the key to your cell ♪
♪ You've got to love your neighbor ♪
♪ Love your neighbor ♪
♪ And let your neighbor love you back ♪
[camera shutter clicking]
♪ Stand tall for the beast of America ♪
♪ Lay down like a naked dead body ♪
♪ Keep it real for the peopleWorkin' overtime ♪
♪ They can't stay livingOff the government's dime ♪
♪ Stand tall for the people of America ♪
♪ Stand tall for the man next door ♪
♪ We are free in the land of America ♪
♪ We ain't goin' down like this ♪
♪ Come on now ♪
‎两位好啊
[Spenser] Hey, you guys.
‎你在找东西吗 警官？
[woman] You lookingfor something, Officer?
‎不 我已经不是警察了‎现在只是一个热心市民
[Spenser] No, former officer.I'm just a concerned citizen now.
‎在干私家侦探？
Doing a little private investigating?
‎我还没有为我的工作想好名称
[Spenser] I haven't really come upwith the title yet for what I'm doing.
‎如果发现与我的调查有关的线索‎告诉我一声
Let me know if you hear anythinggermane to my investigation.
‎你在调查什么 路易莎伯顿探员？
What investigation is that,uh, Agent Louisa Burton?
‎发挥你的想象力
Use your imagination.
‎你是那个因为袭击约翰博伊兰‎而被捕的家伙
You're the guy that got arrestedfor assaulting John Boylan.
[wheezing laugh]
‎哇 你的搭档还真是紧张
Wow. Your partner's wounda little tight, huh?
‎恕我直言 两名金贵的联邦探员‎跑来监视一名黑警察？
You know, no offense, but twotop-dollar Feds tailing a dirty cop?
‎你们俩犯了什么错‎被派来干这个苦差事？
[chuckles] I mean, what did you two doto fuckin' deserve this shit detail?
‎回见
See you later, all right?
[engine starts]
‎很简单 联调局不破案‎只负责管理案件
[Spenser] It's simple. The FBIdoes not solve crime, they manage them.
‎他们在玩一个不着边际的大游戏
They play some big abstract game,
‎想要换取一些‎捕风捉影的大阴谋或大鱼
trying to trade-upfor some vague masterplan,
‎与此同时 像特伦斯这样‎无辜的受害者
-the Terrence Grahams of the world...-[Hawk] Hmm.
‎却被抛在脑后
...they fall through the cracks. Right?
‎毫无正义可言
There's zero justice, ever.
‎我们现在有何进展？
So, where are we?
‎我们查到了三圣帮‎见到了想做交易的联邦探员？
We got Trinitarios, deal makin' FBI.
‎对 还查到一些极度腐败的警察‎想要掩盖一些事
Yeah.
And we got somevery corrupt cops covering something up.
‎也许干掉博伊兰是为了杀鸡儆猴
-[sighs]-Well, maybe killing Boylan was a message.
‎我知道该去找谁了
I know who we gotta go see.
[indistinct chatter]
‎你想怎么样？
What the fuck do you want?
‎还记得上次你试图揍我吗？
You know that hit you tried on me?
‎是谁指使你的？
Who wanted that? [smacks lips]
‎为什么联调局会监视一名黑警？
Why is the FBI tailing dirty cops?
‎城里发生了什么事？
What's going on in the city?
‎我跟你无话可说
I don't have anything to say to you.
‎我就知道你会这样说
I figured you'd say that. [chuckles]
‎喜欢看电影吗 呆子？
Do you like movies, Squeeb?
‎我在这里有朋友 能把手机带进来
I got friends in here.I was able to bring in my phone.
‎让我…我不知道我是否有这个权利
‎你的脸离摄像头远点
‎亨利！
-Yeah. Henry.-What?
‎-干嘛？‎-你的脸离摄像头远点
Move your face away from the camera.
‎-能看见吗？‎-能
-You got video?-Yes.
‎你确定要这样做？
Are we really doing this?
‎确定 快点
Yes. Now.
‎认识她吗？
Recognize her?
‎那是我老婆吗？
Hey, is that my wife?
‎反正不是我老婆
It ain't mine.
‎搞什么？
Hey, what the fuck?
‎多久了？你进来多久了？
How long has it been, huh?How long you been in here?
‎她有多久没被人好好关爱了？
How long has it beensince she's had some real attention?
‎看到那个帅哥了吗？
You see that handsome gentleman there?
‎他是在超市里认识她的
He met her in a supermarket.
‎他问她想不想喝一杯 她说想
He asked her if she wantedto have a drink, she said yes.
‎现在是下午三点 她穿成这样？
Three in the afternoon,she's dressed up like that? Wow.
‎哇 知道她做了什么吗？
And you know what she had to do?She had to get a babysitter.
‎她请了一个临时保姆‎这个时间请保姆真够奇怪的
That's a weird timeto get a babysitter, huh?
‎你那些雅利安国的弟兄会怎么说？
What are all the Aryan brothersgonna say about that?
‎你最好快点 呆子‎她已经喝了四杯了
You better hurry up, Squeeb.She's already had four drinks.
‎去死吧 你想怎么样？
Fuck you. What the fuck do you want?
‎我想要答案 懂吗？
I want answers, okay?
‎叫你的朋友离苏西远点
Tell your friend to leave Suzie alone.
‎亨利
Henry, tell Hawk to walk away.
‎叫霍克走开
‎好的 明白
[Henry] Okay, got it.Hey, Romeo, get outta there.
‎嘿 大情圣 出去
‎你想怎么样？
[Squeeb] What do you want?
‎我知道你有情报 呆子
I know you know things, Squeeb.You got ears on the street.
‎街上有你的耳目
‎博伊兰是怎么死的？
What happened to Boylan? Hmm?
‎我出狱那天 是谁下令揍我？
Who ordered the hit on me on my last day?
‎我只告诉你一个词
I'll give you one word, man,one word only.
‎最好是个好词 朋友
Well, it better be a good word, amigo.
‎仙境
Wonderland.
‎你是说那个赛狗场？
What, you mean the dog track?
[chuckles]
‎你笑什么 呆子？
What are you smiling at, Squeeb?
‎我在想象你的脑袋在人行道上翻滚
I just keep imagining your headrolling down the sidewalk.
‎你他妈的死定了
[chuckles] You're fuckin' dead.
‎科斯格罗夫 你在里面吗？
[Spenser] Cosgrove, you in there?
‎你是谁？
[Cosgrove] Who's there?
‎出来吧
Come on out.
‎你在哪儿？
Where are you?
‎仙境？
Wonderland.
‎他们要在那里建一座赌场
They're building a casino there.
‎价值相当于‎一个产油小国的国民生产总值
It's gonna have the GNPof a small oil-rich nation.
‎-涉及腐败？‎-是的
-[Spenser] And it's corrupt?-[Cosgrove] Well, yeah.
‎你听说过诚实的企业经营赌场吗？
I mean, ever heard ofan honest outfit running a casino?
‎开赌场的目的就是搞腐败
I mean, they are, by design,instruments of corruption.
‎如果我还是罪案记者
If I was still a crime reporterand I wanted to get my head chopped off,
‎想让自己被砍掉脑袋
‎我就会报道黑警察与大政客勾结
I'd be writing aboutthe connection between some dirty cops
‎利用三圣帮的毒品买卖‎在仙境赌场获得一个席位
and some big politiciansusing the Trinitario drug trade
to get a seat at the table of Wonderland.
‎就像某种邪恶的合伙企业
It's like some fuckin' evil partnership.
‎意思是“黑暗”
‎因为仙境财团有足够的钱
Because the Wonderland syndicatehas got enough money
‎让我爆的料见不了光
to bury anything I put out there.
‎好吧 想想看 那些恶警…
All right, picture this.
‎多尼米加街头黑帮
Real bad cops, Dominican street gangs,
‎以及一些最肮脏的投资者相互勾结
and some of the dirtiestinvestors in the game,
‎为堕落的赌徒打造下一个伟大的
all working together
to build the nextgreat family-friendly resort destination
‎适合一家老少的度假胜地
for degenerate gamblers.
‎（仙境）
‎如果我能找到证据呢？
[Spenser] What if I get you evidence?
‎什么？
[scoffs] What? Real, undeniable evidence?
‎无可辩驳的铁证吗？
‎我不知道那是什么样的
I don't even know what that looks like.
‎要想戳破该死的假新闻‎必须要有看得见的证据才行
It would have to be some fuckin' visualto poke through this fake news bullshit.
‎我告诉你
I'll tell you that. Okay? So, we done now?
‎好吗？我们谈完了吗？
‎说真的 这样的谈话会害我被爆头的
Because, honestly,this is the kind of conversation
where a little red sniper dotpops up on my forehead.
‎嘿 你！
[man] Hey, yo!
‎-什么事？‎-你不能来这里
-[Spenser] What's up?-Hey, you can't be here.
‎不能吗？抱歉 这里是私人产业吗？
[Spenser] No? I'm sorry,is this private property?
‎抱歉 我没看见标牌
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't see a sign.
‎我小时候经常跟祖父来这里
I used to come hereas a kid all the time with my grandfather.
‎我以为重新开放了 想来看看赛狗
I thought it was reopening.I was hoping to see some dog races.
‎不 马萨诸塞州已经20年没有狗了
Nah, no dogs in Massachusettsfor 20 years.
‎不 不是这样的‎我经常在马萨诸塞州见到狗
Oh, no, that's simply not true.
I see dogs all the time in Massachusetts.
‎事实上 我就有一只
In fact, I have one.
‎你看 她叫珀尔
Look at that. Her name's Pearl, huh?
‎像女王一样‎我给她取了我祖母的名字
What a queen.I named her after my grandma.
‎你必须离开这里
-Now you gotta get outta here.-Okay.
‎-好的‎-走吧
-Come on.-All right. I'm sorry about that.
‎抱歉
‎祝你们愉快
Have a good one, guys.
[man singing] ♪ Lord ♪
‎请赐予我们的姐妹乐迪莎力量
♪ Please give strengthTo our sister Letitia ♪
-[woman vocalizing]-[organ playing]
‎起立！
-[officer] Present arms! Weapons up.-[pastor] God... [indistinct]
‎举枪！
‎预备！
[officer] Ready, aim, fire!
‎瞄准 开枪！
‎开枪！
Fire!
‎这件事浪费我们太多时间了
We have come way too farto let this take up any more of our time.
‎开枪！
[officer] Fire!
‎猫和铃铛
Cat and the bell.
‎一群老鼠快乐地住在一个谷仓中‎直到有一天
Group of mice live very happily in a barn
‎一只流浪猫开始吃老鼠
until, one day, a feral catstarts eating the mice.
‎于是有天晚上 它们聚在一起
So, they all gather together one night
‎想办法对付这只流浪猫
to figure out what to doabout this feral cat.
-[officer] Fire!-[gunshots]
‎“何不在它的脖子上挂一个铃铛？
[Driscoll] "Why don't we placea bell around his neck
‎这样它一来 我们就能听见”
so that every time he's coming,we can hear him?"
‎一只年老的老鼠说：‎“这个主意太妙了
One of the older mice says,"That is an excellent idea,
‎但是我们该派谁‎将铃铛挂在猫的脖子上呢？”
but whom shall we get to placethe bell around the cat's neck?"
‎开枪！
[officer] Fire!
‎那我们怎么办？
So, what do we do, then?
‎有时候 你必须杀掉那只猫
Sometimes you gotta just kill the cat.
[bell jingles]
[speaking Spanish]
‎听说你刚出狱
-[waiter] I heard you just got out.-Oh, man.
‎-老兄‎-你一定想大吃一顿
Oh, I bet you could usea good meal. [speaking Spanish]
‎我很想你 老兄‎知道我需要什么吗？四个玉米煎饼
Missed you, buddy.Yeah, I need, uh, four burrito.
‎四个玉米煎饼
[waiter] Four burrito.
‎烤牛肉馅的
-Uh, carne asada.-Oh, you like that.
‎-还有鸡肉馅的‎-鸡肉
And, uh, pollo, uh, puerco.And you know what? Chorizo.
‎猪肉馅的‎ ‎再来一个香肠馅的
‎香肠
Chorizo. You got it.
‎没问题 鸡肉
[Spenser] Puerco. And you know what?
[rap music playing over headphones]
♪ I've had a lot of struggleBurning up my tension ♪
♪ So if you wanna make it count... ♪
‎卷饼
-Uh... enchilada.-An enchilada.
‎-卷饼‎-你儿子还好吧？
-How's mijo?-Oh, mijo is fine.
‎我儿子很好
‎我必须问问 我很久没见过他了
I wasn't gonna ask you.I haven't seen you in a while.
‎他星期三在这儿
[waiter continues indistinctly]
‎你妻子还好吧？
-[Spenser] Yeah. Wife is good?-[waiter] Yeah. Muy bien.
‎-还好‎-再来一个…
-What about, uh, quesadilla?-[grunts]
‎芝士馅饼
‎想吃芝士馅饼的话‎你得等着面饼做好
Oh. If you want quesadilla,just gotta wait on the tortilla.
‎芝士馅饼
[distorted] Quesadilla's...[speaking Spanish]
‎我妻子茱莉亚？
[chuckles] Oh, my wife Julia,oh, she's so great.
‎不 她很好
‎是的
Yeah. She's great.[continues indistinctly]
‎她喜欢美食
‎老兄 这里有很多美食
[bell jingles]
[waiter exclaims]
-[grunting]-[customers screaming]
[yells]
[glass shattering]
[screams]
[groans]
-[clamoring in distance]-[man screaming]
[yells]
‎不！
[woman whimpers] No!
[man] Fuck!
[grunts]
‎喂 上车
Yo! Get in!
‎操
[panting]
‎见鬼！
[Spenser] Oh, shit!
‎-你要倒大霉了‎-为什么？
-You're in big trouble.-For what?
‎你开着这辆里维埃拉‎冲进了一家餐厅！
You smashed the Rivierathrough a restaurant!
[sirens approaching]
[engine revs]
‎老兄 你最近经常挨揍
Man, you get beat up a lot.
‎我发现 每次你被痛扁之后
And I've noticed every single timeyou get your face pushed in,
‎都能带点新的线索回来
you come back with justa little bit more information.
‎别说了行吗？
-Would you stop?-I'm just saying.
‎我只是说 我觉得这个办法很好
I don't think it's a very good tactic.
‎他们知道去哪儿找我‎他们会去亨利家找我
They're gonnacome looking for me at Henry's.
‎他们会在亨利家发现亨利
They'll find Henry at Henry's.
‎见鬼
Shit!
‎（茜茜宠物美容店）
[dog barking]
‎希望你带了毛巾 这里不是汽车旅馆
I hope you brought towels.This isn't a Motel Six.
‎我们只待两天 最多四天
Hey. We're here two days, four days max.
‎亨利家不安全
It's not safe at Henry's.Nobody's gonna look for us here.
‎没人会来这里找我们
‎谁不会来这里找你们？
Who won't look for you here?
‎警察、三圣帮
Law enforcement. Trinitarios.
‎哦 好人和坏人
Oh, the good guys and the bad guys.
‎这让我安心多了
That makes me feel much better.
‎这也不是第一次了！
It's also repetitive behavior.
‎嗨 斯宾塞
Hi. [kisses]Spenser.
‎这是你家还是狗窝？
-[dogs barking]-[Hawk] Is this your house or a kennel?
‎都是
[Cissy] Both. I clean dogs,I board dogs and I am--
‎我帮狗洗澡 提供寄养 我…
‎想那样就去亨利家
-Go to Henry's for that.-[Spenser] Hey.
‎别把我扯进去
-Leave my business out of it.-I expected more from you.
‎我还对你寄予厚望呢
‎你应该是他的导师
You're supposed to be his mentor.
‎培养他负责任的思维和行为
Create an atmosphere ofresponsible thought and action.
‎结果呢？你让两个大男人‎到处扮蝙蝠侠
Instead, you got two grown menrunnin' around playing Batman.
‎我们没有扮蝙蝠侠 好吗？
We're not playing Batman, okay?
‎这完全是蝙蝠侠做的事
This is Batman business all the way.
‎让你和这个大块头‎在波士顿东奔西走 扮演罗宾
Got you and big boy over hererunning through Boston all Robin-ed up.
‎我不是罗宾
I am not Robin.
‎还有这位阿尔弗莱德…
[Cissy] And Alfred over here...
‎老天
[laughing] Uh... Oh, Jesus.
‎你是不折不扣的阿尔弗莱德
You are an enabling Alfred.
‎你给了他蝙蝠车的钥匙
You gave him the keys to the Batmobile.
‎那辆里维埃拉可不是蝙蝠车
The Riv is not the Batmobile.
‎好吧 用途都一样
Well, it serves the same purpose.
‎我们真要住在这里？
Are we really gonna stay here?
‎我宁愿冒险被三圣帮干掉
Because I'd rather take my chanceswith the Trinitarios.
‎-至少他们没那么唠叨‎-对
At least they don't talk so much.
No. Because they're too busytrying to shoot you.
‎因为他们忙着一枪崩了你！
‎其实他们更喜欢用砍刀
You know, actually, they prefer machetes.
‎他们很愤怒
Well, they're angry.
‎好吧
Okay, well, I feel so much better now.
‎我现在舒坦多了
‎所以我要走了
So, I'm just gonna go.
‎走吧 孩子们
Let's go, boys.
‎雪球、罗斯科、斯莫基 走了
Snowball, Rosco, Smokey. Let's go.
[dogs barking and panting]
[dog toy squeaking]
‎你饿了吗？
[Letitia] You hungry?
‎何必多此一举？
And why would I? They probably did this.
‎很可能就是警察干的
[sighs]
‎嘿
Hey.
‎你是大力士吗？
Are you a giant?
‎是的
Yeah.
‎你是好人还是坏人？
Are you a good one or a bad one?
‎我是好人
I'm a good one.
‎你能把我的床翻过来吗？
Can you pull my bed over?
‎应该没问题
I think I could handle that.
‎你来把枕头放到床上吧
I want you to put the pillow on the bed.
‎能办到吗？
Can you do that?
‎两个枕头都要
Both pillows.
‎特伦斯会把不想让别人发现的东西‎藏在哪儿？
Where would Terrence keep somethingif he didn't want anybody to find it?
‎我不知道
I don't know.
‎知道他们在找什么吗？
Well, do you have any ideawhat they were looking for?
‎怎么了？
What?
‎你知道他们在找什么吗？
Do you know what they were looking for?
‎不 我不知道
No, I don't.
‎你为什么要帮我？
Why are you doing this?
‎因为这样做是对的
'Cause it's the right thing to do.
[Letitia sniffles]
‎特伦斯…
Terrence...
‎寄了这个给我
mailed this to me the day he died.
‎在他死那天
[sniffles]
‎是窃听装置
It's a wire.
‎我知道这是什么
I know what it is.
‎你听过吗？
[Spenser] Did you listen to it?
‎我不懂怎么听
I don't know how.
‎我懂
I do.
[sniffles]
‎-你有地方可以去吗？‎-没有
-You have some place you can stay?-No.
‎我哪儿也不去
We're not goin' anywhere.
‎我不会让自己被赶出自己家
I'm not getting chased out of my own home.
‎好样的
Well, good for you.
‎听着
All right, look.
‎一有线索我就打电话给你 好吗？
I'm gonna call youwhen I know something, okay?
‎-谢谢‎-好的
-Thank you.-[Spenser] Okay.
‎这个我可以留下吗？
Can I hold on to this?
‎上面有他的字迹
[chuckles] It's got his handwriting on it.
‎当然
[Spenser] Of course.
‎好 我会很快给你打电话 走吧
All right. I'll call you soon. Come on.
‎你不知道这趟浑水有多深
[Boylan] You got no fuckin' ideahow deep this shit goes.
‎那就告诉我
[Terrence sighs] So, tell me.
‎凭我的级别 根本无法获得那条信息‎辅祭男童 要高层才行
[Boylan] Now, that informationis way above my pay grade, Mr. Altar Boy.
But high up.
‎高层
High up.
‎懂吗？罗斯奥斯库罗斯‎只是其中一个参与者
All right, Los Oscuros is justone seat at this fuckin' table.
‎拜托
Oh, come on.
‎联调局那边
The Feds.
‎给我一点好料来刺激他们的胃口
Give me something goodto whet their appetite.
‎你们用三圣帮的毒资干了什么？
What are you guys usingthe Trinitario drug money for?
‎你以为呢？
What do you think?
‎那是我们进入仙境的门票
It's our ticket into Wonderland.
‎办许可证、贿赂、建设
Permits, pay-offs, construction.All that. Dirty cops.
‎贪腐的警察
‎-比如你？‎-对
-Like you?-Yeah, like me.
‎比如我
‎谁在操控这件事？如何运作？
Who's running this thing?How does it work?
‎三圣帮听命于本特伍德
Trinitarios are working for Bentwood.
‎本特伍德听命于麦克林
Bentwood works for Macklin.And they all work for Driscoll.
‎他们全都听命于德里斯科
‎这个他们已经知道了
They already know this.
‎我需要确凿的证据 博伊兰
I need something concrete, Boylan.
‎拜托 老兄 我是帮你的
Come on, man. I'm on your side.
‎让我帮你获得最有利的认罪协议
Let me help you getthe best deal out of this.
‎跟我说说小马快递的事
Tell me about the Pony Express.
‎我就明说了吧
[Boylan] I'll make it clear.
‎三圣帮和“运动哥”查理‎每周跑一趟小马快递
Trinitario street gang and TracksuitCharlie do the Pony Express once a week.
‎你去告诉联调局‎让他们拍下他们能想象到的
You tell your fuckin' Fedsto picture the biggest shipment
‎最大一批芬太尼和氧可酮的运送照片
of fentanyl and oxy that they can imagine.
‎好吧？拿到照片之后‎让他们把那个规模再增加两倍
All right? And when they get that picture,tell 'em to triple it.
‎时间和地点呢？
Where and when?
‎帮我搞定认罪协议 我就告诉你
I will tell you that once I get my deal.
‎三圣帮听命于本特伍德
Trinitarios are working for Bentwood.
‎-我对天发誓 我什么都没说！‎-你是个奸细 博伊兰
I swear to God, I didn't give anything!
You're a rat, Boylan.
‎本特伍德听命于麦克林
[Boylan] Bentwood works for Macklin.
‎告密者没有好下场 对吧？
Bad things happento tattletales, don't they?
‎他们全都听命于德里斯科
[Boylan] And they all work for Driscoll.
‎我什么都没告诉他们 我发誓！
I didn't give them anything, I swear!
‎这是我最喜欢的时刻 该死的奸细
This is my favorite part, you fuckin' rat.
‎所以你要上空手…
I see you got kara... Excuse me,karate, after school today, right?
‎抱歉 今天放学后‎你要上空手道课 对吧？
‎是的
Yes, sir.
‎-下课后你能自己回家吧？‎-能
You gonna be able to getyourself home from there?
Yes.
‎我要你五点前回家
-[Driscoll] I need you home by 5:00.-Yes, sir.
‎-是‎-不许晚了
-[Driscoll] No later.-Yes.
‎-是‎-下午五点 你什么时候回家？
-5:00 p.m. What time you comin' home?-5:00.
‎-五点‎-拜托你别晚了
Please don't be late.Your mother's killing me about this, so...
‎不然你妈会杀了我
‎待着别动
Stay right here.
‎斯宾塞
-Spenser.-[Spenser] Hey.
‎-嘿‎-怎么 迷路了吗？
[Driscoll] What are you, lost?
‎没有 只是碰巧来到附近
Nah. Just happenedto be in the neighborhood.
‎好吧
Okay. Okay.
‎你到底来干什么 斯宾塞？
[inhales deeply] The fuckyou doin' here, Spenser?
‎我知道仙境的事了 兄弟
I know about Wonderland, brother.
‎我知道你陷得很深
I know you're in deep.
‎你有证据吗 斯宾塞？
You got any proof, Spenser?
‎有
Yeah. Too much.
‎证据太多了
‎不过你知道 我认识的那个好警察‎他仍然在你的…
You know, the good copthat I know, if he's still in--
‎好吧
-All right.-[grunts quietly]
‎跟联调局达成认罪协议‎告诉他们真相 免得伤及更多人
Cut a deal with the Feds, tell themthe truth before more people get hurt.
‎像条汉子一样服刑
You do your time like a man, brother.
‎兄弟
‎就像我那样
Like I did.
‎为了乔希 做个英雄
Be a hero for Josh.
‎滚蛋
[Driscoll] Get the fuck outta here.
‎我就知道你会这样
That's what I figured.
‎像我一样
‎再见 室友
-[car door opens]-Bye, roommate.
-[car door closes]-[engine starts]
‎三圣帮听命于本特伍德
[Boylan over speakers] Trinitariosare working for Bentwood.
‎本特伍德听命于麦克林
Bentwood works for Macklin.And they all work for Driscoll.
‎他们全都听命于德里斯科
‎我们怎么办？
What are we gonna do?We're gonna get this done?
‎我们搞定这件事 伯顿探员
Agent Burton, just use the tapeto clear Terrence Graham's name.
‎用这卷录音带‎帮特伦斯格林汉洗刷罪名
‎这卷录音带？还不够
This tape? It's not enough.
‎你什么意思？就算没有录音带…
What are you talking about?Even without the tape.
‎凭那批毒品 就足以依据RICO法案‎将仙境一网打尽了
The drugs are enough physical evidence
for a RICO case againstthe whole Wonderland crew!
‎抱歉 我明白你的感受
I'm sorry. I understand how you feelbut I can't tell you any more.
‎但我只能告诉你这么多
‎老天
Oh, my God. Now that's bullshit.
‎屁话
‎你想帮助那个警察的家人吗‎斯宾塞？那就别插手
[scoffs] You wanna help that cop's family?
‎我们有更大的目标
Walk away. We've got bigger fish to fry.
‎我们是联邦调查局
We're the FBI. You push us,
‎把我们逼急了‎我们会让你和乐迪莎吃不了兜着走
we will make so much crapfly around for you and for Letitia,
‎让你回到沃尔波尔监狱
that you'll go back to Walpole.And CPS will...
‎让我帮你获得最有利的认罪协议
[Terrence] Let me help you getthe best deal out of this.
‎跟我说说小马快递的事
Tell me about the Pony Express.
‎我就明说了吧
[Boylan] I'll make it clear.
‎“运动哥”查理和三圣帮‎每周运一次毒品
It's Tracksuit Charlie, movin' drugswith the Trinitarios every week.
‎这就是小马快递
That's what the Pony Express is.
‎女士们好
Hello, ladies.
‎你们都比你们刚来时更漂亮了
Lookin' more beautifulthan you did when you got here.
‎有人找你
[woman] There's someone here to see you.
‎谁？
Who?
‎不！
No, no, no! Okay, Spense.
‎-好吧 斯宾塞…‎-跟我说说小马快递 查理
[Spenser] Tell me about the Pony Express.
‎想老实交代吗？
[muffled grunting]
‎我想知道一切 谁开车 开什么车
[Spenser] I wanna know everything.Who's drivin'?
‎他们来自何处 时间和地点‎我要你全盘交代 查理
What they're drivin'?Where they're comin' from? When and where?
You're going to tell me everything!
[muffled grunting]
‎-嘿 老兄 他们会砍掉你的脑袋‎-是吗？
Hey, man! They will cut your head off--
-[Spenser] Oh, really?-[gurgling]
‎他们开什么车 查理？
What are they driving, Charlie?
[groaning]
‎冷藏车 来自新罕布什尔
Refrigeration van.Coming from New Hampshire.
‎走高速公路 毒品藏在冷藏罐里
Okay. It's coming down the pipes.
It's hid in the refrigeration tanks.
‎-什么时候？‎-藏在…明天
-[Spenser] When?-Tomorrow.
‎-几时？‎-今天！
-[Spenser] When?-[Bentwood] Today! Noon.
‎-中午‎-哪天中午？
-[Spenser] Which one?-[Bentwood gasping]
‎哪天 查理？
-What day do you meet, Charlie?-[Bentwood] Today!
‎今天！
[tires screech]
-[hip-hop music playing over speakers]-[speaking Spanish]
[continues speaking Spanish]
[horns blaring]
[tires screeching]
‎打扰了 先生 你没事吧？
Excuse me, sir. Are you okay?
‎天啊 你浑身是血 让我看看
Oh, my God. You've got bloodall over you. Let me see?
[grunting]
[Hawk] No.
[metal clanging]
‎见鬼
Oh, shit.
[breathes shakily]
[speaking Spanish]
‎-你忘了后座那个‎-我忘了？
-You forgot one in the back.-I forgot one in the back?
‎驾驶员负责查看后排
It's the driver's responsibilityto check the back.
‎这是谁定的规矩？
[Hawk] Who makes these rules?
‎嘿！
Hey. Hey! Hey!
[grunting]
‎你们死定了！
You... You dead.
Yous is dead.
‎见鬼
Oh, shit.
‎每一罐都装满了
Every single one of them is full. Huh?
‎那些警察就是用这个钱‎入股仙境赌场的
This is how the cops are buyingtheir way into Wonderland.
‎老天爷
Jesus Christ! I haven'tdone drugs in 20 years.
‎我已经20年没碰毒品了‎我都不知道这是什么
I don't even knowwhat I'm lookin' at here.
‎芬太尼、氧可酮、可卡因
[Hawk] Fentanyl, oxy, coke.
‎相当于新英格兰一半的毒品
It's half the drugs in New England.
‎这样做不会激怒他们吗？
Isn't this just gonna piss 'em off?
‎等他们进了联邦监狱‎肯定会大为光火 绝对的
Yeah, it's gonna piss 'em off oncethey end up in federal prison, absolutely.
‎我不知道这样够不够
Uh, I don't know if it's enough.
‎你不知道这样够不够？
You don't know if it's enough?
‎如果我给你一张他们拿着毒品的照片‎你会说照片不是真的
If I gave you a photographof them smiling and holding it,
‎如果我给你一盒录像带‎你会说是伪造的
If I gave you a video tape,you'd say it was doctored.
‎要是我带着手捧毒品的他们进入法庭
If I walked them into courtwith the drugs in their hands,
[dog barking]
‎-情况不妙‎-妈的
-Shit!-This is not good.
‎那家伙认出了我们
That dude ID'd us.
[barking]
-[Spenser] Jesus Christ.-Jesus Christ, man...
‎林戈 怎么回事？
Ringo, what's wrong? What's wrong, baby?
‎怎么了 宝贝？‎怎么回事 宝贝？什么事？
What is it, baby? What's up, baby?
‎什么事 林戈？
-What is it, Ringo?-[barking]
‎那是谁的货车？
Whose van is that?
‎霍克的 他找到工作了
That's... It's Hawk's. He got a job.
‎-是的‎-我在帮他忙
-Yeah.-I'm just helping him.
-It's just like a side hustle thing.-[Cissy] Uh-huh.
‎算是副业
‎你知道林戈退休之前是干什么的吗？
You know what Ringo here's job wasbefore he retired?
‎-知道它的主业是什么吗？‎-什么？
-Do you know what his main hustle was?-[Hawk] What?
‎它是一只缉毒犬
He was a narcotics dog.
‎答对了 林戈
-[continues barking]-Bingo! Ringo.
‎嘿 别放它进来！
-Don't let that thing in here!-Oi! Oi!
[Ringo whimpers]
‎你把毒品带进我的车库？
You brought drugs into my garage?
‎帮帮忙 跟亨利回屋去
Just do me a favor.Go back in the house with Henry.
‎你干了什么？
What did you do?
‎亨利？
Henry?
‎斯宾塞
[Cissy] Spenser!
‎-亨利呢？‎-他不在
-He's not here.-Why is he not here?
‎为什么不在？
‎他想回家
He... he wanted to go home.
‎-他说他想回…‎-我特别叮嘱你们待在这里
-He said he wanted to go.-I specifically told you to stay here!
‎-他去哪儿了？‎-他想回家
-Where is he gonna go?-[Cissy] He wanted to go home!
‎天啊 开什么玩笑
Oh, my God. You gotta be kidding--
‎（亨利）
[vibrating]
‎见鬼 他想和我视频
Shit, he's FaceTiming me.
‎亨利不会用视频
Henry doesn't know how to FaceTime.
‎斯宾塞
Spenser.
‎你想怎么样？
What do you want?
‎我想和你坐下来谈谈‎打开天窗说亮话
I want us to sit down and talkand throw everything on the table.
‎把问题解决了 免得…
Work this out before...
‎我不得已干掉亨利
I have to kill Henry here.
‎嘿 别碰他
Hey. Don't touch him.
‎听到了吗？
You hear me? Do not touch him.
‎不要碰他
‎-这些家伙是一群白痴‎-斯宾塞
These guys are a bunch of idiots, Spenser.
‎他打我的眼睛 斯宾塞
‎你在哪儿？我马上过来
Where are ya? I'll come there right now.
‎仙境
Wonderland. One hour.
‎-给你一个小时‎-我这就去
I'm on my way.
‎把我的毒品带来
And bring my drug shipment.
[sighing heavily]
‎我们怎么办？
What are we gonna do?
[breathing heavily]
‎你们跟我去吗？
You're with me?
‎好
Okay.
‎听着 仙境就像一个废弃的堡垒
-Look.-[Hawk] Mmm.
Wonderland is basicallylike an abandoned fortress.
‎只有一条路可以进入 就是这里
And there's pretty muchonly one way in, right here.
‎现在是中午 可以藏身的地方不多
It's the middle of the day.There's not a lot of places to hide.
‎我们必须把亨利救出来
We're gonna have to getHenry out of the way.
‎不过我有个计划
And I got a plan.
‎有点不合常规 你必须相信我
It's a little unconventional.You're gonna have to trust me.
‎不 那把炫酷的枪不是给你的
No, no, no.No, you don't get the cool gun.
‎霍克这个名字‎一听就是拿散弹枪的狠角色
Aw. Hawk is the name ofa motherfucker with a shotgun.
‎斯宾塞像是搞税务的
Spenser does your taxes.
‎很好笑 是个好笑话
That was good. I'll give you that one.
‎好吧
All right.
‎我真的很想知道‎你为何要抓我当人质
[Henry] You know,I'd really love to understand
the process of why you took meas a hostage.
‎没有人会来救我
Nobody's gonna come for me.
‎我已经黄土埋到眉毛了
I got about three minutes left in me.
‎没人会在乎我的死活‎我自己都不大在乎
Nobody gives a shit if I live or die.
I don't even care much if I live or die.
‎你打了我的眼睛 干嘛打我的眼睛？
You hit me in the eye.What you hit me in the eye for?
‎我好好坐着 没有招惹你
I was sitting, minding my own business.
‎我知道你来了 还跟你打招呼‎你却打我的眼睛
You come in, I say, "Hello,"and you hit me in the eye.
‎-我要上厕所‎-亨利
-I gotta go to the bathroom.-Henry.
‎-干嘛？‎-亨利！
-What?-[Driscoll] Henry.
‎小心我堵住你的嘴 老家伙
I will gag you, old-timer.
‎不管堵不堵嘴 我都要上厕所
Gag me or not, I still gotta goto the bathroom.
‎谁是这出闹剧的导演？
Who's running point on this shit-show?
‎你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?
‎斯宾塞呢？
[Driscoll] Where's Spenser?
‎你们这些无耻之徒‎你们就这样对待一个老人？
[Cissy] You degenerates.This is how you treat
‎一个智力低下、可怜的老人
an old man, a poormentally-challenged old man?
‎来吧 我们走 亨利
-Let's go, Henry.-I'm not mentally challenged.
‎-我才不是智力低下‎-闭嘴 亨利 你受惊了
Shut up, Henry! You're in shock.Come sit down.
‎-过来 坐下‎-你来干什么？
-You got a...-What're you doin' here?
‎你的前列腺像西柚那么大 过来
...prostate the size of a grapefruit.
‎-他们性侵你了吗？‎-没有！
-Sexually?-No.
‎你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
‎-他们玩你的屁股了吗？‎-没有！
-Did you engage in ass-play?-No!
‎-你可以告诉我‎-贱人 够了
-[Cissy] You can tell me---Bitch, please.
‎别玩了
Stop playin'.
‎斯宾塞在哪儿？
Where's Spenser?
‎我他妈的无法告诉你
I can't tell you that.
‎我会爆掉你的头
I will blow your fuckin' head off.
[bird screeches]
[engine roaring]
‎搞什么？
What the fuck?
[birds squawking]
‎（黑贝蒂）
‎见鬼
Holy shit!
Whoo-hoo!
[grunting]
[grunts]
-[tires squeal]-[grunting]
[engine sputtering]
[country music playing on radio]
[groans]
[gunshots]
-[Spenser] Oh, my God.-[gunshots continue]
‎这就是你的计划？
This is your plan?
‎我的计划就是撞死他们
My plan only went as faras the entrance, okay?
‎妈的
-Shit!-[Henry] Spenser!
[gunshots continue]
‎我得抓住德里斯科
[pants] I gotta get to Driscoll.
‎好 去抓他吧 我掩护你
-Okay, go get him. I got you.-[Spenser] All right.
‎好
[grunts]
[groans]
‎他在那边！
[man] He's over there!
‎见鬼！
[Spenser] Oh, shit!
‎德里斯科！
Driscoll!
‎见鬼！
Shit.
[door bangs open]
‎喂！
Yo!
[both grunt]
‎这样出拳就对了！
That's how you throw a fuckin' punch!
-[yells in Spanish]-[yells]
[indistinct yelling]
[grunting]
[breath trembling]
[machete clatters]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[Driscoll groans]
‎结束了
It's over.
‎你想毙了我吗？
What, are you gonna shoot me?
‎你是如何杀害‎特伦斯格林汉警官的？
How did you kill Officer Terrence Graham?
Huh?
‎你是怎么做的？
What'd you do?
‎把枪放在他的手中 伪装成自杀吗？
Wrap his hand around the gun,make it look like a suicide?
‎让你的手下帮你按住他？
You have your boys hold him still for you?
‎警察杀警察？
I mean, cops killing cops?
‎什么时候这样都行了？
When did that ever become okay?
‎嗯…
[sighs] Well...
‎你打算怎么做？
So, what are you gonna do?
‎你知道我会怎么做
You know what I'm gonna do.
‎让你坐牢
You're goin' to prison.
‎不过我先要给你上一课
First, I'm gonna teach you a lesson.
‎是吗？什么课？
Yeah? What's that?
‎坐牢的警察必须学会打架
Oh, a cop in prison'sgotta know how to fight.
‎相信我这句话
You take my word for that.
‎来吧
-[gun clatters]-Let's go.
‎好啊
Oh, let's.
‎-我受够你的废话了 斯宾塞‎-来啊
-[sighs] I'm sick of your shit.-Come on.
‎-你以为你很特别？‎-上啊！
-You think you're special?-Let's go.
‎你不是什么唱诗班的男孩
Oh, you're not a fuckin' choirboy.
‎你是个吃牢饭的！
You're a fuckin' jailbird! Fuck you!
‎去死吧！
[both grunting]
‎操
[Spenser groans] Fuckin'...
‎我给过你机会 兄弟
I gave you a chance, brother.
[Spenser grunting]
‎去你妈的机会
-[Driscoll] Fuck your chance.-Fuck!
‎操！
[panting]
[grunts]
[groans]
‎你没本事在牢里活下去‎知道为什么吗？
You ain't got what it takesto make it in prison, you know why?
‎因为你太软弱
'Cause you're weak.
[both grunting]
‎来啊
[breathing heavily] Come on.
‎你愚蠢的正义感在现实世界中行不通
Your stupid Serpico morality,it doesn't work in the real world.
‎你总是他妈的太天真！
-[grunting]-You were always so fuckin' naive!
‎自以为能够帮助受害者
Huh? You thoughtyou could help the victims?
[grunts]
‎你连狗屁都帮不上
You ain't helping shit.
‎总是没完没了地需要同情‎拜托 全是屁话！
Always some endlessfuckin' need for sympathy.
Oh, please, that's shit!
[coughs]
‎-听到了吗？你谁都帮不了‎-操
You hear me?You ain't helping no one.
[Spenser softly] Fuck.
‎世上没有正义 斯宾塞！
There's no justice, Spenser!
‎只有强者…
There's only the strong and the weak.
‎和弱者
[panting]
[chuckles]
‎你的尸体会在我抛尸的地方被人发现
They gonna find your bodywherever I dump it.
‎警察会用粉笔绕着你画圈 你死定了
They gonna put chalk around you, boy.You gonna die.
‎亨利也是
Henry, too.
[panting]
‎而我会自由自在地走在大街上
And I'm gonna walkthese motherfuckin' streets!
[inhales sharply]
‎永远
Forever.
-[bones snap]-[Driscoll screams]
[both grunting]
[groans]
-[Spenser grunting]-[groaning]
[panting]
‎知道吗？坏蛋
You know what, bad guy?
‎我今天要伸张正义
I'm gonna serve some justice today.
‎我要以公民身份逮捕你
I'm gonna make a citizen's arrest.
‎你被捕了
You're under arrest.
-[grunts]-[handcuffs click]
‎坏人的台词就留着吧‎等你进了联邦监狱 跟你的狱友去说
You save the bad guy talk for the boysin whatever federal prison you go to.
‎替我问候他们
You can tell 'em I said hello.
[grunts]
[sirens wailing]
[helicopter whirring]
‎（不是假新闻）
‎我靠
Damn.
‎你们要倒霉了
You boys is fucked.
‎要倒霉了
[chuckling] Fucked.
‎（《警察被捕‎面临贩毒、暴力、谋杀等指控》）
‎突发新闻
[news anchor] Breaking news.
‎剧情惊人逆转 震惊南波士顿
A shocking turn of eventshave rocked South Boston.
‎联邦调查局与波士顿警局‎今晚联合宣布
The FBI, in cooperationwith the BPD, announced tonight
‎波士顿警局的数名高级警官
that several top-rankingBoston police officers
‎已经被捕 罪名是贪腐…
have been arrested on chargesof corruption and racketeering.
‎…和敲诈
‎其中的首要指控是陷害‎波士顿警局的特伦斯格林汉警官
Chief among these charges is the framingof Boston Police Officer Terrence Graham.
‎波士顿警局已经对格林汉的家人‎做出了正式道歉
BPD has releasedan official apology to Graham's family
‎并且宣布 已经撤销了‎针对特伦斯格林汉
and have announced that Terrence Grahamhas been posthumously cleared
‎与约翰博伊兰警监的惨死‎相关的所有指控
of all charges relating to the gruesomedeath of Captain John Boylan.
‎波士顿警局将为这位逝去的英雄
The fallen hero will receivea Boston PD burial
‎安排隆重的荣誉葬礼
with full honors.
‎爹地
Daddy.
‎此外 还为他的幼子罗兰
A scholarship is also being set upfor his young son Rowan.
‎设立了一项奖学金
‎我们将继续跟进报道这条重大新闻
We'll have more on this top storyas it continues to develop.
["Sweet Emotion" playing]
♪ Sweet Emotion ♪
‎嘿
Hey.
‎来吧
Come on.
‎你希望霍克来看你吗？
You want Hawk to come to see you, huh?
‎知道吗？你说的话她一个字都听不懂
[Cissy] You know she doesn'tunderstand a word you're sayin'.
‎我说的话她全能听懂
She understands everything I say.
‎不 她只是等着你喂她吃的
No. She's just waitingfor you to give her a treat.
‎你很漂亮
You look good.
‎我知道
I know.
‎-想带我去吃午饭吗？‎-你想吃什么？
You wanna take me for lunch?
‎我想让你给我买一只龙虾
-What do you wanna eat?-I want you to buy me a lobster.
‎你打算吃掉它还是…
Are you gonna eat it or...
‎不 我会将它砸在你的脸上
No, I'm gonna throw it in your face.
‎对 我会吃掉 我饿死了
Yeah, I'm gonna eat it. I'm starvin'.
‎走了 珀尔！
-Come on, Pearl. [whistles] Come on.-[Pearl barks]
‎来吧
‎你这次表现不错
[Cissy] You did good this time.
‎知道吗？对 听着很甜蜜
[Spenser] You know what? That was sweet.
♪ Sweet Emotion ♪
‎（龙虾）
‎敬大难不死的一家人
Here's to a familythat stays in the game, huh?
‎这是我老爸最爱喝的水果啤酒
[all speaking indistinctly]
‎-我讨厌龙虾‎-这是你人生的巅峰
[laughing]
‎吃龙虾庆祝的生活
[muffled] The celebratory lobster life.
[laughing]
‎我在一艘捕龙虾船上干过10个月
I worked on a lobster boatfor ten months...
‎很久以前的事了
long time ago.
‎拖上来一箱箱可怜的龙虾时
Seen them pulling up box after boxof those poor lobster bastards,
‎它们用小眼睛瞪着我‎像是长着爪子的迷茫的小孩子
with their little eyes staring at melike little lost children with claws.
‎-就像这只？‎-没错
-Like this one?-Yeah.
‎很可爱啊‎所以你才会变成现在这样
It's charming. It's what makes you you.
‎你想采用历史性的世界观‎谈谈你那个热狗去过哪儿吗？
[muffled] You wanna takea little historical review
of where that hot dog of yours has been?
‎-你完全不了解我‎-好恶心
-You don't know anything about me.-[Cissy] You're disgusting.
‎-太凶残了‎-警方今天逮捕了
-[man] Hey, Frodo.-[Cissy] Fuck, yeah!
‎圣艾丹教堂被烧毁了？
Whoa. Saint Aidan's church burned down?
‎两年前的事 当时你在坐牢
Two years ago, when you were in prison.
‎波士顿消防大队长福雷‎正被警方带出来
Boston Battalion Chief Foley is beingbrought out right now by the police.
‎我是被人陷害‎我对天发誓 不是我干的
I'm a firefighter. I was set up.
I swear to God, I didn't do this.
‎马蒂福雷？
Marty Foley?
‎-亨利 他是我的高中同学‎-见鬼
-Henry, I went to high school with him.-Oh, shit.
‎换个频道！棕熊队正在打比赛
Somebody change that channel.The Bruins are playing.
‎两名波士顿消防员在烈焰中丧生
[reporter] Two Boston firefightersdied in the blaze.
I have kids. I would never do this.
‎我对天发誓 我绝不会做这种事
I swear to God,I would never do this. I need help!
‎我需要帮助！
‎-不行‎-棕熊队 谢了！
-No.-The Bruins, please!
‎我需要帮助！
I need help!
‎-我需要帮助！‎-不行
-I need help. I need help.-[Cissy] No. No!
‎棕熊队！
[Henry] The Bruins!
["Foreplay/Long Time" playing]
♪ It's been such a long timeI think I should be goin', yeah ♪
♪ And time doesn't wait for me ♪
♪ It keeps on rollin' ♪
♪ Sail on ♪
♪ On a distant highway, yeah ♪
♪ I've got to keep on chasin' a dream ♪
♪ I've gotta be on my way ♪
♪ Wish there was something I could say ♪
♪ Well, I'm takin' my timeI'm just movin' on ♪
♪ Takin' my time ♪
♪ Oh, just movin' along ♪
♪ Takin' my time, yeah ♪
♪ Takin' my time ♪